♪～
～♪
BEASTMEN SHOULD DIE
10 years have passed since the enforcement of the Beastmen Special Zone.
There's strong antipathy against...
...Beastmen Territory, and a protest at the front of the Congress is currently ongoing.
Now departing. All standing passengers...
...please hold onto the handrails.
Ever since we established the Beastmen Territory Law...
...we have managed to develop Animacity, a city where beastmen can...
...truly live as themselves.
That's it!
We are currently cooperating on the Beastmen
Special Zone Development Project.
Beast New Age
SYLVASTA Pharmaceutics
Damn it...
Ouch...
Damn beastman...
We can easily see through you!
This is the path that everyone who escapes Animacity takes.
You'll bite the dust if you stick around here!
Monsters like you are multiplying...
It's a goddamn eyesore!
Drop dead!
Excuse me!
Could you stop that~?
That kid is one of my precious customers.
Please be gentle.
Suddenly shooting an arrow at me...
Isn't that... a bit rude?
Let's dispose of these guys already.
It'd be a pain in the ass if you kill them, so try to hold back a bit.
The path to Animacity is ridded with beast hunters.
But you don't have to worry. I will be taking you there.
W-who are you?
I'm the one who extends her hand to beastmen in trouble...
...a loving volunteer, Mari Itami!
That's kind of shady.
That hurts.
So how much is it?
I said I was a volunteer, though...
You're the type to charge me afterwards, right?
You're not too charming, are you?
If I had any charm, I wouldn't be here right now.
You're certainly right.
Guess I'll take all the money you have then.
Are you serious?!
It's the price for your life, so don't be stingy about it!
Am I right?
Don't say it so happily.
Is that city really only for beastmen?
Yep! Animacity.
Are you also an outlier?
Don't worry.
You'll be able to sleep properly from now on.
Yeah...
Alright, we're here.
Once you get off the boat, we're back to complete strangers.
Got it. Thank you!
What's this? It's way too quiet...
It's a festival!
It's the mayor!
Mayor Rose!
Mayor, let's go!
It's been ten years since Animacity was built.
The gap between beastmen and humans hasn't been closed yet.
Regardless, this city continues to be the safe haven for beastmen.
These past ten years, and the following ten years...
No, for the sake of the future that lies beyond...
Let's celebrate the anniversary!
Everyone is really a beastman!
There's no need to run anymore!
Ah, I'm sorry... Huh?
Whoa...
What a nice smell...
It's the smell of beasts filled with joy and happiness.
What?
Celebrate. It's the festival that beastmen have waited for for a thousand years.
O-okay...
There are many types of people, huh...
He's crying... and he's scary.
What's up with that guy?
Mayor, it's from the Prime Minister, Shiramizu.
Congratulations on the ten-year anniversary, Mayor Rose.
It is all thanks to your comprehension.
Ahaha, don't get me wrong, though.
The Beastmen Special Zone isn't impenetrable.
If you beastmen start behaving dangerously...
I don't know what could happen, or when...
I'm sincerely counting on you.
Same as always, huh. I can't tell if he's celebrating or threatening us.
Even so, ten years have passed.
To Rose Barbarei's ten-year fight.
To ten more years of Animacity.
This is pretty strong!
Oh my, being a glutton? I knew you had more.
You're that weasel!
Not a weasel! A mink!
Really?
Don't confuse me with those cheap-fur animals!
Okay...
I said "all your money", didn't I?
Kids are so treacherous lately...
I won't give you any more money.
We're back to complete strangers, right?
Do I really look that selfish to you?
That makes me sad... So sad...
Ah! A thief!
Oh, poor thing.
Be careful~ Animacity is full of sneaky people like that.
Did you really...?!
You sure you wanna argue? The pickpocket is getting away.
Damn it!
Someone! Catch that pickpocket!
Hold it!
Where'd he go?
God damn it!
Move it!
Hurry up, grandpa!
Crapcrapcrapcrapcrap...!
Ouch...
You're the crying guy!
Wait, you're crying again.
It was you?! The one wrecked the beastmen festival?!
It wasn't me! I just punched a pillar!
And you made it explode?!
Are you for real?
I'm telling you it wasn't me!
That guy...
He was sneaking around those pillars!
That guy?
It seems this was a misunderstanding. I'm sorry.
Huh?
The hell is up with that guy?
Right! The pickpocket!
What?
A bummer, isn't it? It was a smell-less bomb!
You can't tell even if you're a beastman!
Whoa!! The hell is this?!
That hurt...
Is this guy immortal or something?!
Spit it out. Why did you interrupt the festival?
Ouch...!
Huh, that was quick.
What's wrong, Satou? Did your trap fail?
Be careful...
That damn wolf... He completely outdid my bomb!
It seems they're pros.
I see...
Humans!
You bastards were bought out by humans, huh?
How could you tell, huh?
You cannot cover up such a deep human smell.
What an effective nose you have!
You were bought out by anti-beastmen humans...
You're pretty stuck on that "bought out" thing.
It doesn't matter if it's a human or a beastman.
When it comes to contracted work...
...we'll do it properly!
That's all there is to it!
Is that... why you ruined... the festival...?
You gotta be kidding me!
You damn...
W-whoa!
That sin...
You'll atone for it with your life.
You damn beastmen who sold their souls to humans...
You bastards aren't even worth using my claws on.
My fists are more than enough!
Bring it on!
You better not regret it!
Let go!
You, who lost the pride of a beastman...
...you don't need the pride of a deer!
Stop it... I beg you...!
My antlers... Anything but my...!
Stop right there, you greenhorn.
Branding me as a greenhorn...
Don't move!
If you move, this kid's life is done!
Whose life is done, you said?
Hold on!
That's horrible!
That's enough, isn't it? Those poor people!
Don't try to stop me. These guys ruined the festival.
They're beastmen too, though! This is...
These guys were hired by humans.
They're a disgrace to all beastmen.
That much is right.
Stop it!
I said stop it!
That's enough!
Why are you fighting against your own people?
Wasn't this city a "beastmen paradise"?
That's exactly why.
Humans are enemies to this city.
Beastmen hired by humans are the same.
Not all humans are like that!
All humans are the same.
That's not true!
Because...
...I'm also a human!
That's right...
I am a human...
...I was a human!
With that appearance?
♪～
～♪