I am human... I was human!
You look like a tanuki.
I-I'm not! I'm a raccoon!
If you were a raccoon, you'd have stripes on your tail. You're a tanuki no matter what.
I don't like tanukis!
Follow me.
He got here first, huh...
♪～
～♪
Hold on!
Where are you taking m--
Ah, uh, I-I mean...
How long do you plan on staying that way?
Hurry up and change back to a human.
That's...
You can't?
I thought he was older...
Huh?
What's wrong?
No one's in their beast forms...
That's a given.
I mean, just a bit ago...
That's because that was a festival. This is normal.
Whaaaaat? Are you kidding?
What do you mean?
I thought everyone used their beast form all the time...
Don't say something so human-like.
Well, I am a human.
We're here.
Yep, she's a beastman.
What? Just with that?
A beastmen marker is a simple but effective way of examination.
You're without a doubt a beastman.
That's not true! I'm a human!
Even without using a marker, you can clearly tell you're a beastman, though...
I'm really a human!
I was a normal human a year ago...
Then I became like this out of nowhere...
That's not possible.
Humans are humans. Beastmen are beastmen.
It's decided from the beginning. It doesn't change like that.
I'm sure it's a disease or something!
A disease?
Yeah! A disease! A beastman disease!
There must be people like that in this town, right?
There's no one like that.
Well, I've never heard of a case like that.
Lately, it seems there have been strange diseases regarding human delusions...
...so I recommend getting check--
Not that kind of disease!
Gem, don't say it like that!
I swear you have no delicacy at all...
I'm really sorry. You're Ms. Kagemori, right?
Ah, yes! I'm Michiru Kagemori.
I'm Melissa.
You see Gem like this, but he's the Director for the Beastmen Life Association.
It's also our job to help newcomers with their troubles.
In any case, you'll go to the council tomorrow for your Beast Registration...
...so make sure to fill this in, yeah?
I-I'm telling you, I'm really not a beastman! A Beast Registration...
Even so...
That's it! My student credential!
Student credential?
My blood type and species are written in my student credential.
Beastmen and humans have different blood types...
...it's clearly written so there are no mistakes when transfusing blood, so...
Right... It was in my wallet...
Oh bother... You'd better give up on that.
No waaaay!
If something gets taken from you in Animacity, the chances of getting it back are slim.
How about you go sleep? You look very tired...
In any case, this'll have to be enough for today.
The bed is clean, so...
It's enough! I've always been homeless, so it's fine.
If there's anything you don't get, ask Shirou over here.
Whoa! Ouch...
Kuro...
We're getting up early tomorrow. Get some rest.
Shirou isn't too sociable, but he's not a bad guy.
Oh, he's named Shirou...
Oh, you haven't asked him?
Shirou Oogami, he's our social worker.
Shirou will take you to the council tomorrow.
Oogami...
We don't have a bathtub, but you can use the shower, right?
Oh, yeah!
This is not what I thought would happen...
It's packed...
See ya.
Eh? you're leaving?
I also have some things to attend to. I just took the chance to take you here.
Do the rest yourself.
Move!
I'm in a hurry.
I come first!
What? Are you kidding me?!
What? What's going on?
Younglings like to show off their power.
No no no, that's not what I mean...
Are there no rules?
There are.
The stronger one wins. It's a simple rule.
T-there's no way...
Your turn won't come up if you just stand there.
Sigh... I didn't think it this city would be like this...
I feel I've seen him around...
Oh, could he be...?
Thank you for capturing the bomber.
They were terrorists hired by an anti-beastman organization.
If money is involved, even our fellow beastmen would accept such a job.
It's sad.
Those guys are a disgrace to beastmen.
By the way, I have one more request.
I knew it!
What are you doing?!
Give me back my wallet!
Iunno what yer talkin' about!
There's no way you don't know!
You stole it from me yesterday!
Ya think I remember that far back?!
Far back?! It was yesterday!
In this town, it's pointless even if you're talking about yesterday.
Uh... Where have I...
Ah, you're that weasel--
Mink!
Not a weasel, but Mari the Mink!
Tanukis really are half-witted, huh?
See ya never!
So you were an accomplice!
You just "happened" to see me? You're an accomplice so you came to help him, right?
It was just a coincidence, a coincidence... It's because this city is so small!
Gimme some credit.
Who do you have to thank for making it into this city?
I paid you properly, didn't I?!
Okay, okay...
Trust is the priority in this business, after all.
I'll tell you as a service.
For lost things, Rabbit Town is the place.
Everyone gathers around there.
Rabbit Town?
Yeah. Pay a visit to Gran Grandma over there.
This feels nothing like a "rabbit" town...
Huh? What's up with ya?
E-excuse me...
Do you happen to know where Gran Grandma could be located?
You got some guts showing up in your beast form here.
Don't play dumb.
In gang terms, changing to your beast form means you wanna fight.
Showing up in beast form means you're looking for a fight, ain't that right?!
Y-y-you misunderstand!
I can't control it myself, so I can't go back from this form!
You can't go back?
You're not a baby! Are you mocking me?
I'm not mocking anyone! I really can't!
I was a human up until last year...
So you were...
Did you think such a poor excuse would fly?
I can prove it!
There's a student credential in the wallet that was stolen from me yesterday...
I came here to look for that!
Why do you think it's here?
I heard it from a weas... from Ms. Itami.
She said you might know...
Huh, so it was Mari...
Ah, that's it! That's my wallet!
Look at the student credential inside and you'll see! I'm actually...
You're a student?
She asked if you're a student!
T-that's right...
So that means...
You can at least read and write, right?
I can...
I don't mind giving this back, but...
In exchange, can I ask you for a favor?
Teach these kids to read and write.
There were children here...?
Betrayed by men...
People like me... Washed up people...
They all end up in Rabbit Town.
Beastwomen who have nowhere else to go...
...more or less have to choose the dangerous path.
These kids must also strongly feel that bitterness.
If they can read and write...
...they can open up the path for a better tomorrow.
If you do that for me, I'll return your wallet.
Got it.
I will do it!
Can anyone read this?
Is there?
Yes! You!
Poop!
Okay. That's somewhat wrong.
This is "Mi", "Chi", "Ru"!
It reads Michiru! That's my name.
Okay, can anyone write their own name?
What's your name?
Youta.
Youta, I see.
This is "Youta".
"Yo", "U", "Ta".
Try writing it!
That's right! That's "Youta". It's your name.
Who else wants to write their name?
This place reeks of women like always.
Alright, let's first memorize all hiragana, okay?
Hey, are you listening?
Wow, you're good at that! Is that a wolf?
No, it's Ginrou-sama.
Ginrou-sama?
That's bad, Michiru. You don't even know Ginrou-sama?
Nope, I don't know.
It's the God of Beastmen!
When a beastman is really having a hard time...
A silver wolf will come to the rescue!
The story's been around since forever.
Was that it, then...?
Michiru, did you see it?
No way! Really?!
N-no, I didn't get a good look at...
Huh?
Hey, Kusakabe. What are you doing here?
For business, obviously!
Who would come here if it ain't for work?
Sure, "work"...
You came for the money anyway, right?
Didn't I tell you the money isn't here yet?
"It's not here~"
...yeah, right!
If ya don't have it, then make it!
You women...
Who do ya have to thank for being able to live in the Yakuza business? Think about it real hard!
...What did you say?!
You wanna go?!
Don't be childish, Kusakabe.
B-Boss...
I don't wanna fight with my woman colleagues.
It's just a matter of paying up.
Showing your face around here is a rare sight for sure, Flip.
I thought I'd pay a visit to the fabled Gran Grandma once in a while.
Sure you did.
Even if you come out, I can't pay what I can't pay.
Is that so?
I heard you stocked up on some new animals.
If you prepare those...
...the money will start coming in.
Why do you know that?
Did you think you could hide it?
Well, it seems the higher-ups have also caught wind of it.
What?
After all, women's work...
...is pretty obvious.
If you don't prepare them before packing them up, they won't even amount to a thousand yen.
You got that, didn't you?
You're able to keep yer business thanks to us!
What's going on? What are you planning to do with us?
Thought I'd bring you all on a trip.
It can't be... You're gonna sell us?!
Would've been nice if they managed to read some more...
...so they could sell even higher.
Turns out I had to dispatch them all now.
So that's why you asked me to...
They're your children! Are you for real?!
I don't recall saying they were my children.
Then, these kids...
They're children wo got lost...
...or whose parents died when they got to Animacity.
Are you... are you serious...?
That's horrible!
Weaklings step on those weaker than them to live on.
That's the kind of place this is.
Ginrou-sama, save us...!
Asking a god for help won't solve anything. We have to fend off for ourselves!
Everyone, hold on!
What an undisciplined tanuki.
Roll up the cable!
This is it, huh.
No way!
Look, the driver's seat is closer now!
We mustn't give up!
No one will help us because we're in this city!
We must extend our own hands...
...and grab onto each other...!
No matter how hard you try, you can't close that distance!
My... my arms are extending!
Nngh...! Oh! I think I grabbed onto something!
Aah! My hands are stretched out! Gross.
That's amazing!
But your hands are gross.
That "gross" was uncalled for! Ah, but I think...
I grabbed onto some sort of lever!
Come on...!
Pull on the lever...!
What... what's going on?!
What a mess!
Come on, pull!
Alright, everyone, run!
Hold it!
What an interesting skill you have.
You're really not a beastman, are you?
Run!
Ngh... Let go...!
Make it quick.
Got it.
...the hell are you?!
Ginrou...
There is no forgiveness for those who sell beastmen to humans,
...even if it's a woman.
Don't say that!
I surrender. Be gentle with older people.
Looks like another success, Oogami.
We'd be in serious trouble if you didn't...
...manage to catch the tail of that beast gang.
It was a request from the mayor.
Where are the kids?
Who's that?
She's a newcomer. We're tending to her in the association.
You got a rough welcome as soon as you got here, huh.
We'll be protecting the kids, so you don't need to worry.
We have an institution for orphans, after all.
What is it?
Unforgivable! Trying to sell children...
Even if you're a beastman, don't you have a human heart?!
Heh, I see.
It really seems like you're not a beastman.
What do you mean?
Living as a woman in the world of beastmen...
Tell me that once you're know how rough it is.
Why were you there?
You saw it all from that building above, didn't you?
Yeah.
Why didn't you come to help back then?
You knew we were gonna be sold, didn't you?!
There was no evidence yet.
The only way to arrest them was to catch them in the act.
What would you do if you didn't make it in time?
What would you do if the boat sailed?
We could've been sold!
Did you even think about those children?
I never miss.
I will protect every beastwoman and child.
Woman and child...
Are guys really all that? Are men really all that?
Look at that! I'm a human!
"I never miss", yeah right...
Do you see your mistake?
I hate beastmen and this damned city!
I'll heal from this damn disease and get the hell away from this city!
♪～
～♪