♪～
～♪
I did it! I got the audition!
That's great! You can do it, Nazuna! Do your best!
Nazuna?
"To Mom and Dad:"
"Rather than being holed up in this room..."
"...I'm going to live in Animacity."
"Please don't worry about me. -Michiru"
Good morning, Mr. Gem!
Nice weather, isn't it?
How is that room? It's way better than the rooftop, is it not?
Yeah! Thanks!
Mr. Gem, what's that big building over there?
Hm? Ah, it's the Medical Center.
Sylvasta Medical Center.
It's under direct management of Sylvasta Pharmaceutics.
There's a laboratory and a hospital there.
Sylvasta's...
I see... If I go there, I could ask about my disease...
H... Hey, what the hell are you doing?!
You little... It won't open!
Why? Hey, hang on, what is this?!
Why?! Let me out! Hey!!
Be quiet.
Why?! It won't open...
I finally understand that you were a human.
So what?
Your existence is dangerous.
Huh? Why do you say that?
People would panic if they found out that a human can turn into a beastman.
Don't go out until we find out the details. I'll be bringing you food.
W-What are you talking about?! I really don't get you!
Believe in me. I'll protect the peace of the beastmen.
No, even if you say it all cool like that, I can't trust you!
It's gross!
Open up...! I'm going to the hospital...!
No.
One step outside and I'll kill you.
S-So you don't care about my peace?
Remodelling this early in the morning? Must be tough.
Mayor.
It's... the Mayor?
The bomber?
Yes.
We received a report...
...from the police saying the Medical Center received a threatening letter.
And earlier this morning...
A truck loaded with Sylvasta medicine was blown up.
A bomb?
Uh... It's my ears this time? Oh well.
"If you have the money to make..."
"...a beastmen hospital and use the latest equipment..."
"...use it for the sake of humans" is what the culprit said.
So it's those anti-beastmen again.
The police also tried to track the smell of the bombs, but...
...because of the impact, the smell was severely muddy...
...so they couldn't follow any trails.
Your excellent sense of smell is way more...
...reliable than the police investigation team.
I beg you. Look for the bombs.
There are people admitted to the Medical Center.
We must avoid a fight.
If the hospital is blown up... I might not be able to recover from my disease!
That's bad... Really bad!
Help me, Mayor!
That was a voice just now.
Nope.
Help me! He trapped me here!
It's Kuro. He recently remembered how to mimic.
Move that.
Oogami?
Mayor! This guy is responsible for abducting a woman!
Hey!
He said he'd kill me if I went outside! That's blackmail!
It's for your sake and beastmen's sake.
You're Michiru Kagemori.
Just looking at you, you're a splendid beastman!
It's hard to believe you were a human until just recently.
So... you knew?
I have to know everything about Animacity.
That's the mayor's duty.
I see. It was Gran Grandma.
Confidentiality is also part of my duties.
Excuse me...
Let me help with searching for the bombs.
Why?
Sylvasta Pharmaceutics have cutting edge technology, don't they?
If that's the case, they might be able to cure my disease, right?
We don't know if it's a disease yet.
But it's true she used to be a human.
The chances of it being a disease aren't zero.
In any case, letting her outside is dangerous.
If anti-beastmen humans find out about her... Who knows what would happen?
I don't want to stay put.
All I did before coming here was hide and do nothing.
Holing up in my room...
When I ran away, I kept hiding from the beastmen hunters...
...and I finally made it into this town...
..but living in the shadows again... I refuse to do that.
Look...
We need more people. Let's let her help.
You can take care of being Kuro's contact, right?
Contact?
You can't tell she was a human just by looking at her.
As long as she moves within Animacity, there shouldn't be a problem.
However, the fact that you were a human stays here.
Got it.
Would you also let me drop the charges against keeping you in captivity?
...Okay.
Okay, here.
A phone! It's been so long!
If Kuro finds something, contact Oogami.
These are bomb fragments left on the scene.
Sylvasta Pharmaceutics is part of a world-leading...
company group, the Sylvasta Conglomerate.
The mayor says humans have the same rights as beastmen...
...so Animacity can get big fundings.
There are lots of humans who dislike that.
There are rumors that Sylvasta Pharmaceutics...
..is collecting beastmen data and making a profit off of it.
Not all beastmen are welcome there.
So why did you take the job?
Huh?
I thought you didn't move if it wasn't for beastmen's sake.
I can't refuse a request from the Mayor.
It's Oogami. I located the bombs.
There are six bombs. Let the bomb squad go look.
You go to the Medical Center.
The Medical Center too?
No, there are no bomb smells there, but just to be sure.
The real target of the bombers must be the Medical Center, after all.
Hold on, I'm going too!
There are 6 bombs.
Let's hurry up.
Huh... Kuro?
Ah, h-hold on!
Hurry up!
Don't fret.
The police are too busy dealing with the bombs.
In any case, this is the last time!
That's cold. You should see this as a good thing!
A good thing? What are they up to?
Hey! Who's eavesdropping over there?!
Ah, damn it!
Who is it? Come out!
Heh. Capture her.
She saw us! She might've heard something.
Ya think we'd let a child like that run away?
However, I swear I've seen her before...
Come on, pick up!
Alright, that's the last one.
It's her!
Her?
...! That's...!
I knew it! It's her!
Yeah...
Hey, kid. Why were you in such a place?
Uh... I got a bit lost...
Oh? Did you happen to hear something important?
Gotta teach a good ol' lesson...
...to annoying kids like you.
Stop that.
Y... You're Oogami!
You bastard!
Die!
Go. I won't kill you. Not today, that is.
Ngh... We'll remember this!
Thank god I made it. Kuro let me know.
Damn it! I called you multiple times!
I'm sorry. Why were those guys chasing you?
So, I saw those shady guys sneaking in some luggage through the back of the Medical Center...
Who are they?
A gang.
A gang?
They were sneaking in some goods in cooperation with the staff...
An explosion?!
You wait in the association!
No way! If they blow it up I'll be in serious trouble!
It's dangerous!
Okay, I'll admit it then.
I was really a human... But right now, I'm a beastman.
What are you saying?
You'll protect all beastmen, right?
Then protect me, too.
Because I'm also a beastman.
...You're persuasive.
This is horrible.
Oh, Oogami.
This is the Medical Center Chief, Mr. Yaba.
This is also the handiwork of those bombers, huh.
The police is responsible for this, you weren't able to stop it!
Let me investigate.
He's an advisor who's helping with the investigation.
Is that alright?
Hm. Feel free.
Oogami overlooking this, though...
I efficiently tracked the bombs' smells, so why...
This is...
Did you figure something out?
There's no smell.
Mimura, it's that girl! She came back!
What?
If that's the case...
I got it.
P... President...
The Medical Center was blown up?
What a scary world.
Yes. The research data management section was blown up.
However, the hospital's data management is hosted in another building, so it's safe.
I see. That's a relief.
Restoring the place of the explosion is first priority. Do it at any cost.
Make sure not to leave any traces of an incident.
Not a trace, Mr. Yaba.
...Understood.
What a pain.
Chief Yaba.
Can we make some questions?
What do you want?
I'll make sure you take responsibility for this!
We investigated the place of the incident...
We couldn't confirm any traces of the culprit.
Are you avoiding me?!
It's not just the culprit.
There wasn't a single smell at the scene.
That's impossible.
It's impossible to have all smell disappear under normal circumstances.
You have to use a chemical to do such a thing, after all.
Mr. Yaba... In this laboratory...
You're able to create such a thing, isn't that right?
That's ridiculous.
Are you doubting me to hide your own incompetence?!
I saw the staff here cooperating with a gang earlier.
Doesn't that mean you're involved as well?
You had bombers blow up the lab to erase the evidence...
Hey, hey... Do you really trust what this guy's saying?!
You can always reach the culprit if you follow the residual smell left on the scene.
Because there are no smell-less beastmen.
But at the crime scene...
There was a period where there were absolutely no traces of any smell.
...And your hands are lacking any smell right now.
Ever since the lab was blown up.
His smelling skills are adopted as evidence under the provisions of the Special Beastman Territory.
Mr. Yaba, can we have a chat at the station?
Shirou!
Don't move!
If you move, I'll strangle this kid to death!
Run, Mimura!
Chase him!
Your claws won't tear through my skin!
You're covering up the case for your own benefit.
My bare hands are enough for such a cowardly man!
To you who abandoned the pride of a beastman...
...that horn is useless!
Stop it. I beg you! My horn... Anything but my horn...!
Let that kid go!
Don't move!
If you so much as move an inch, I'm dropping this kid!
You can't escape if you do things like this!
It's all your fault! If only you weren't here...
...it wouldn't be this complicated!
If you value this kid's life, prepare a helicopter with one hundred million yen for me to escape!
Don't be ridiculous!
Kuro!
Don't underestimate a chameleon's sight!
If you do unnecessary things, I'll really kill this kid!
Where's the money and he helicopter?!
This dude is serious!
If I can extend my hands like before...!
Shirou! Shirou!
I'm alive.
Would you move?
Oogami! It's best if you don't move.
Get some treatment at the Medical Center.
No, I'm fine.
Can you move?
Yeah.
Good grief.
Are you really okay?
I won't die.
Uhm. Thank you for saving me.
I promised.
I'll protect all beastmen.
Yaba and Mimura confessed.
They were cooperating for embezzlement.
Then they realized the higher-ups found out...
...and they blew up the data system of the Medical Center.
They hired people to set up fake bombs...
...so they could erase the embezzlement data.
Is that really all?
What do you mean?
That Mimura guy's malice... It was stronger than that.
If only you weren't here...!
I mean, blowing up your own lab to protect yourself...
It's really odd.
That's how they try to cover up what's inconvenient for them.
Adults, I mean.
Are you talking about me?
Who knows~
I'm sorry. I won't lock you up anymore.
I mean, you were so worked up over it...
I don't want to be put in the same bag as those guys.
So don't go telling anyone else about your beastman disease.
I know.
Ms. Michiru, I'll search for a treatment for you.
She's in charge of researching beastmen genetics.
She also has the first PhD on it.
I'm a politician now, though.
I have a good relationship with Sylvasta Pharmaceutics, so it's a good chance.
I had them make a backup for the Animacity establishment as well.
I see.
Be careful with Sylvasta Pharmaceutics. They're very fishy.
Why?
No reason. Just my nose telling me that.
Ah, it's your... "wild intuition", eh?
Are you making fun of me?
No waaay~
Gentlemen!
Our research here is over.
Are we moving?
Yeah. I'm going, too.
It's time I take a look at how the beastmen base is for myself.
It's been ten years since Animacity was established, huh.
What a big milestone.
♪～
～♪