♪～
～♪
Damn it, it's no use!
What are you doing?
Uhm, I was trying to go back to my human form...
You're a weird kid.
Ah, more importantly, you have a call from the council.
A call?
It's your beastman registration credential and your insurance card.
Formalities were still in order, so...
Consider it as a thank you for the bomb incident.
It's been a bit rough for you, right?
Thank you.
With this, you're now officially part of Animacity.
Welcome to the Beastmen Capital.
Ah, yeah.
Ah, right!
I'm giving this back.
Don't worry, you can keep it.
...But I can't use it.
It doesn't connect to the outside internet, does it?
No matter how many times I tried, only the council site came up.
That's correct. Information on human society is restricted by the Special Beastman Territory Law.
That's unfair!
Ms. Michiru, this is a good chance, so please remember this.
Beastmen, or rather, the Beastman species is different from the Homo Sapiens species.
Thanks to a special gene called "Beast Factor"...
...we can freely change our bodies.
In ancient times, beastmen were worshipped by their tribes...
...and made them look like beast gods.
They wanted to be like gods.
That's why your beast form is decided based on ancestry.
A lion's child will be a lion.
If two species breed, only one of the parents' attributes will prevail.
The resulting child will be either a lion or a tiger.
It won't be a liger.
Of course, humans without a beast factor can't change into a beastman.
But I...
That's right. The impossible happened to you.
Beastmen have always lived having no contact with the Homo Sapiens... Humans.
Be it a forest or a mountain, a deserted island, a desert...
But due to human environmental development, we had to show ourselves to them whether we wanted to or not.
Since the discovery of the beastman species, there were a couple of conflicts, but we somehow managed to establish Animacity.
But that's when you came in.
I researched your genes.
They are different from a regular beast factor.
It's unstable, but an explosion-like cell division occurs when you change shapes.
That's probably the reason behind your ability to freely change your form.
It's still just a hypothesis, though.
Is it curable?
I don't know that yet.
Give me some more time.
In any case, please stay with the association.
Okay...
I kinda get it, but I also don't...
...though I can't use this, that's for sure.
Heya, tanuki girl!
Ah, it's the weasel...
I said I'm a mink.
Anyway, I got my hands on some real good stuff! Wanna see?
No, thank you.
What?
Illegal phones that can jump over the Animacity firewall...
If you just want a SIM card, it's 50% off.
It's a time-limited sale~
Ten, nine...
B-but I don't have...
Eight... Seven...
Can you put it in my tab?
Not my tab, but Shirou's!
My daughter got mad at me recently so I bought an e-cig...
...but that's useless.
I'm telling the truth.
…I don't know who distributed the Medical center supplies...!
You were seen by Shirou Oogami.
That's your problem.
Hey, Kusakabe.
How do we deal with men who can't even take responsibility for their own mistakes?
Flip. I have business with that man.
You'll have to wait.
We're not done here yet.
Stop it!
Aah, stop i--!
It seems your business is gone.
Hey guys!
Having to go out in a hurry is rough, eh?
For that occasion, I'll be recommending some cosmetics!
Even if you're out of time, you'll look like you put a lot of effort into it!
Humans are living here?
The foundation I used today is this...
Excuse me!
Ah, excuse me...
A-are you...
W-what the hell?
Hey, you bastard.
Who ordered you to get close to the lady?
Uh... Who's the lady?
I mean...
Where am I?
Don't play dumb.
You knew she was The Family's daughter so you closed in on her, didn't you?
The Family?
Do you mean...
...that one gang?
Seems you've remembered something.
Spit it out.
What do you want getting close to the lady?!
That's not it! I just happened to see her in Facelook...
Facelook?
Do you know about Facelook?
I happened to come over here just recently...
You come from the mainland?
No way! That's awesome!!
Really? Where? Tokyo? Shibuya? Harajuku? Omote-sando?
More from the countryside...
I'm Nina. What's your name?
Mi... Michiru.
So you were a beastman...
You mean humans were watching me?
Amazing!
I show myself as a human on the net.
To hide my shiny beast form~
You can go now.
Hey, is your dad...
Ugh, I hate my dad.
That's my grandpa.
He was caught by humans before I was born...
...boiled in soy sauce and eaten. It's what my dad says.
What the hell.
Right? There's no way!
Just recently I was caught listening to human music...
...so now I'm not allowed outside.
They say it's "indecent and harmful".
I know! Let me show you something cool!
These are my treasures!
They are things that washed up on the beach, or gifts I got!
Is that nostalgic? Do you know what that is?
It seems just one piece washed up.
They don't have cables, right?
(NIGHT RUNNING starts playing)
Hey! You're on a diet until the audition, aren't you?
I can eat this!
You're really different from everyone else.
People who come here don't wanna talk about the mainland.
Do you wanna go back?
I can't return looking like this.
I want to go back.
Michiru?
I'm back...? I'm back! How?!
No tail anymore so I can pass through gaps!
I can put hats on!!
That's right. This is the real me!
Were you always in beast form?
Ah, uh... Y-yeah!
I forgot how to return to my human form...
So, you can go back home.
You can go to the mainland!
Nina!
Hold on, Nina!
You know, a girl named Lisa from Facelook...
...is holding a home party.
I'm invited!
Are you serious?
If you hop onto my back, we'll be there in no time!
If we return quickly, there's no problem, right?
Why do you want to go over there so bad?
Only knowing this island my whole life... I don't want that.
Besides...
The city is sparkling.
Let's go.
Nina!
Papa is back home!
Nina~
Nina?
My deepest apologies!
It was farther than I thought.
Oh no! We gotta hide!
Eh? Why?
There's police who help beast hunters, too!
Hey, you girls!
It's pretty dark around here, so be careful!
Michiru... You worry too much.
How did you live here?
Ah, it's there!
(NIGHT RUNNING starts playing from the speakers)
Michiru!
So this is the taste of macaroons, huh?
Ah, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You're... glad you came, right?
Yeah. I'm glad I was able to come back.
Hey, Nina!
You're Nina, right?
You really came! We're finally meeting in real life!
Ah, are you Lisa?
We're finally meeting~!
Oh, that's bad...!
No way... No way no way no way!
You were a beastman all along? And you're also a dolphin? So cute!!
Help me out, guys.
Let's go!
Everyone, listen.
We got a very special guest for our beastman costume party!
A beastman... Nina!
Did you forget yours? I'll let you borrow these.
The pain and suffering that Nina has had to face due to discrimination...
...we can't even being to comprehend it.
I'm sure it was very hard on you.
Eh? I mean, I'm not really...
Let's praise the beauty and courage of Nina's way of living!
Shirou, you got a call!
Oogami, do you know where Michiru is and who she's with?
She's hanging out with Flip's daughter over there.
If The Family finds out...
...it'll be a big problem.
You want me to take them back home before anything happens.
Thank you.
You asshole! You wanna die that badly?!
I have business with Flip.
I'm busy now. Move.
Do you plan on starting a war with humans?
So what if I do?
I'll bring your daughter back.
And why would you do that?
You can either leave it to me or argue pointlessly here.
Make your choice.
Hm. I'll wait until midnight.
If she doesn't come back before then, you're all turning into minced beef.
Did you see that?
Nina, let's go home.
Why?
I don't... I don't know, but...
Something's off.
This isn't the place I wanted to return to.
Why? Everyone's nice, aren't they?
Don't tell me you don't like this just because I'm the popular one.
What are you talking about?
If that's the case, just go and say you're a beastman too.
I'm not going back home.
What am I doing...?
Yeah.
I don't care if you left Animacity.
Do what you want.
But return Flip's daughter immediately.
What? How do you know that?
Flip's ready to start a war with humans.
I'm heading over there soon. Figure it out before that.
Got it?
H-hold...! Why so sudden...?
Seeing you entrust work to someone else...
The sky might as well fall.
Damn it.
That's the first time I've seen a beastman!
Yeah, me too!
But isn't it actually kind of scary? She's like half a beast, isn't she?
RIght? I wouldn't be able to live with her!
What are you doing?!
Nina looked tired, so I thought to put her in the water.
I mean, she's a dolphin, right?
Ah, Nina!
Nina!!
Are you okay?
Let's go home.
Yeah...
Michiru...
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I'm the one who's sorry.
If you didn't go to the human world...
...you would still like it.
I should've stopped you.
I don't particularly hate it.
I mean, it was really sparkling!
I see.
Didn't you want to return there?
That's right. I wanna leave Animacity.
But not right now.
I wanna know more about beastmen.
I feel I need to.
That's why I still wanna be in that city.
You bought things using my tab.
Work and pay it back.
What? Make it a present!
It's my birthday, you know!
I don't care.
Cheapskate.
Cheapskate?
Stingy wolf.
Thief tanuki.
That's-- I mean...
…An immortal body, and someone who can transform their body beyond a beast form...
There's no way they're normal beastmen...
...these two.
"Michiru, happy birthday.
-From Mom-"
♪～
～♪