♪～
～♪
Last night's game ended on a 6-2 with Wild Calling taking the win...
Night Runners, the losers' death count amounted to three.
In that game, the last remaining dodo beastman...
...died from the double play, so dodo beastmen are officially extinct.
Next up...
Aren't you able to return to your human form?
That's true... but changing into my human form...
...I feel like I'm wearing heels all the time.
You know what I mean?
Not at all.
It's more convenient to be in this form when needed.
So being a tanuki is more convenient...
Ms. Melissa!
Are there no basketball circles or a basketball association in this town?
Basketball?
I wanna have a match!
My body grows dull if I don't play, after all...
Matches, huh... There are!
Oh, really?
See? A match!
This is baseball, though. It's no basketball...
Well, they both involve chasing a ball and running around...
...so they're not so different, are they?
Hello to the 5-6 baseball fans of Animacity!
The pink flamingos are as cute as always!
Bears, the bear team facing them, looking as foolish as always...
...here to update their growing consecutive losses!
Wow, everyone's playing in their beast form!
Heeeeeey! Heeeeeeeeeeeeey!
Heeeeeeeeeeeeeey!
Alright...!
I-I-I... It's a miracle ball!
Ah! Damn it...
Changing from attack to defense, the pink girls are defending now!
Hit!
Out~
For real?!
Hold on! Something just came out of that girl's feather, something pointy and stabby!
So what?
The hell are you?
You're one of those bitches who proclaim justice and tell on people! A justice bitch!
Would you look at that, tanuki girl. We meet again.
Ah...
M-I-N-K.
Not a weasel, but Mari the Mink.
I didn't say anything yet!
So who are you betting on?
Betting?
You still don't understand a thing, as always.
Animacity's baseball is a complete fight to the death gambling game.
They're beastmen who would kill if it means they win.
It's gambling that makes spectators rejoice every time someone dies or wins.
Wining or losing, living or dying.
That's the baseball of Animacity.
You're kidding...
Alright, it's time for the girls to attack!
And the flamingo hits!
Straight to the pitcher!
It's a hit!
A direct hit to Winnie the Pooh, Bears' pitcher!
He's being carried on a stretcher!
Oh~ Without a pitcher, you can't go on!
The bear team only has 9 people~
Doesn't that mean we win?
Coach!
Coach! C-o-a-c-h!
Yes, nice, batting, a hole in one~
Pitcher change with that girl!
Eh? Me?
No no no...!
It's okay, don't worry.
Let's close up the gap!
Yeah!
Change of pitcher for the Bears!
No matter how you look at it, it's a newbie tanuki girl!
Even so...
Hey bitch!
Yeah, you! Would you hurry up~?
You're also a tanuki on top of being ugly, I feel so bad I'm about to cry!
But I have an appointment with a nail salon afterwards, so I have no time for sympathy~
If you're not gonna throw, you might as well go back to Kachikachi-yama! How 'bout you make a mud boat as well~?
Actually, you're all so ugly, I can't help but feel bad...
Sneering at people, laughing about things you were born with and can't change...
...putting labels on people and acting like you've already won!
Sexy strike~!
For real?!
An incredible miracle ball is born!
Shit!
Strike!
Strike! Strike! Strike!
Batter out!
We're almost at the end!
The Bears might actually have a chance!
The batter's the miracle ball tanuki girl!
I have to make a mud boat in Kachikachi-yama, so~
Would you hurry it up~?
Damn you!
Hit~!
She got it!
She got it! What a surprise!
A turnaround victory for the Bears!
Oogami, have you ever tried baseball?
No.
What about baseball gambling?
I want you to find evidence of the growing baseball gambling in the city.
Flip from The Family is in charge of the gambling. That's the unspoken rule, isn't it?
It's hard to deal with that.
Dodo beastmen went extinct yesterday, due to baseball.
What sort of beastmen will go extinct next thanks to baseball, I wonder?
We don't have any money♪
But we don't have any dreams either♪
But if it's about desires♪
We have more than plenty♪
It's a bit cramped, but come in!
Whoa, it's really cramped.
Our water supply was cut so I brought water from the park.
Here you go.
I have a request for you.
Please become the pitcher for the Bears!
We beg you!
H-hold on!
Look, I'm not even a bear!
Raccoons are also welcome!
We don't discriminate against types of bears.
I'm really glad we won today!
We've never won other than by default.
With you here, we could actually win the championship!
Championship...
I really can't play baseball. I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It was a short-lived dream...
If we don't have a pitcher, we can't play.
Baseball is all we have, too...
Being born here means muddy water for life...
For life...
Okay, I get it! I'll do it!
However, absolutely no killing!
Eh? Why?
I'll play baseball but I won't participate in a killing game.
Okay, no killing, but what about hurting?
No.
Twisting a finger?
Cutting nails?
Not even a hangnail?
No, no, I said no!!
Hello to the poverty-stricken and people with free time.
Today's baseball match:
The uneasy-looking Bears who spent all their luck of their lives in the last match to turn it around...
...and the heavy-weight stars of the baseball gambling world, the Buffalos!
Alright, play ball!
The poor, foolish Bears are attacking!
An unusually sluggish ball... They got it!
Running against each other... First base, safe!
The Bears coach is making signs! They're pretty easy to understand!
Hey, they're catching on!
The Buffalos' defense at all once...!
Wow, it was really a bunt.
Easily out!
He's signing for a bunt again! Is he serious?
Or is it a sophisticated trap?
It's a bunt.
Out! Stew and bead and bears! Stupid bears~
Their fourth batter is...
...the famous tanuki girl!
Another see-through sign!
Is he being exceedingly helpful?
It's the tanuki woman's gorilla swing!
A long hit! The bulls are chasing it!
The tanuki gorilla girl is fast!
It's like she has cheetah legs!
The bulls are throwing it back home!
Who's faster, ball or cheetah? Ball or cheetah? Cheetah or ball?
Ball or cheetah!
Safe!
Wow, who would've thought the poor, worn-down Bears would win?
Like throwing money away, it's a win with no profit for anyone!
You were supposed to lose, right?
The profits for today!
Who would bet on such a weak team for baseball and fighting like the Bears?
If baseball's popularity goes down, our business goes down with it. That would be a problem, wouldn't it?
Next time... Next time we'll definitely lose!
Next time we'll drop you into the ocean!
What were you doing in that shop?
I was eating pizza, obviously.
I'm looking for proof on baseball gambling.
Would you testify?
You can't keep on living if you defy The Family.
Even if you hang around them, they'll just turn you into food.
For us beastmen...
...to make a living out of baseball, this is the only path to take.
You're on the right field today.
And you're the pitcher.
Eh, me?
Coach, Michiru is our ace! Michiru should be the pitcher!
That's right!
Shut up! I'm the coach here!
So you better obey me!
I can't be the pitcher!
You'll be okay. We'll all protect you.
If we win this one, the finals are next! You wanna win the championship, right?
Yeah!
Let's get this win!
This is Dante, your new teammate!
They say he's the first beastman player.
We don't accept beastmen in this hotel.
Beasts should go to the zoo!
Beasts should go outside.
Beasts don't need a bench, do they?
Goddamn beast.
Hurry up and die, you goddamn beast.
The pitchers for the Bears today is Arai Rascal!
I don't think you can win even by using an oven glove.
Because his rivals are...
...the strong tiger group, Tigers!
It's oooooooout... of the playfield!
No one's chasing it! They won't make it!
There she is!
The cheetah dash of the unwavering tanuki girl!
She's using the sad nature of animals who chase moving things fully in her favor!
Ah, almost there! She's so close!
...Whoa, no way!!
That fool...
Nice catch!
And just like that, the Bears take the win!
An immense profit of a hundred yen to ten thousand yen!
The eels are replaced by the Bears in popularity!
The finals are finally next!
Hey, gorilla tanuki.
I recall you promising not to use your powers in front of people.
Don't get cocky. What happens if someone finds out?
I mean, yeah...
If anyone finds out about your abilities...
The town might as well disappear before you get the chance of curing it.
Those Bears... They're a bit dumb and useless, but...
...they love baseball. That's the first time I've ever met people like that.
It's like I forgot about my beastman disease as soon as we started playing baseball...
You're okay with forgetting about it?
Not at all...
...but ever since coming to this city...
...no, ever since getting this beastman disease, this is the first time I've had any fun.
Help!
Good news! The Bears' popularity is increasing.
"They're cute, like an unruly child", they say.
If you lose the next match, I'm willing to forget and forgive.
If you defy me, you'll become fish food.
I give up...
Where did I go wrong to end up with a life like this...?
I'll die either way...
Hello to all gambling addicts.
We've finally come this far.
The finals for the Animacity Baseball League begin now!
The once foolish but now the star of the slums, the Bears...
versus the kill-before-killed, butchering vermin corps, Killer Animals!
If ya don't wanna die...
Go back home and suck on some honey, little cubs.
Play ball!
It's the tanuki girl, full of motivation!
The mad dog is using a cracked bat, a super bat!
The tanuki throws either way!
There it is! The shotgun batting!
Ah! Huh? Huh?
It's a series of rough plays!
As expected of Animal Killers!
Three out! The Bears are showing no resistance.
Such a lethargic baseball!
Nngh... Coach!
...He's gone!
Hey, what's wrong, everyone?
Nothing much...
Aren't you hiding something from me?
I-I-It's not like we're hiding the fact that we'll get money if we lose.
Are you dumb?!
What do you mean?
If you lose against the Killer Animals, we will give you this.
Hold on! Are you fixing the game?!
I dunno if we can win...
...but we can easily lose.
Wasn't it your dream to win the championship?
Getting your sight clouded by money and easily throwing away your dreams...
How stupid can you be?
We're stupid either way!
We've been poor since we were born, and we'll keep being poor!
What's wrong with getting some money to rise up from a hellhole like that?!
This is Saotome.
What?! The money from the safe was stolen?!
Are you stupid?!
All the money from the gamblers was in there!
You goddamn fool!
The money we bet was stolen?!
What will happen with the money I bet?!
Give it back!
Who would watch baseball with no money involved?!
What happened? The venue is bustling with energy!
The match has come to a halt!
The match isn't over yet!
Are you running with the tail between your legs?
Are you that afraid of losing?
Don't be cowards!
This town's baseball is all about winning, losing, living or dying, isn't it?!
If that's the case, then go ahead and fight...
...fair and square, with all your might!
With this one shot♪
We'll turn it all around♪
We Bears♪
Are the star of the bears♪
Let's close the gap!
Yeah!
You got a nice ball there, don't you, tanuki girl?
If you manage to dead-ball me, I'll sue you and make society a living hell for you!
Of course!
We don't do killing games here.
We play baseball!
Would you look at that! The match continues!
You...
Please! Let me go!
It's a hit! Will it go through?
They made it! It's a home-run!
The Bears are cornered by one point!
What a development! Will they turn it around?
This has become an unprecedented, historical baseball match!
People from all over the city are gathering around to see the match for themselves!
There's a one-point difference. Killer Animals are in the lead!
What? C-c-c-coach?!
Where were you until just now?!
Singing again? I don't wanna bunt!
Huh? Do it?
Just do it? Give it your all?
Do your goddamn best!
The game starts now! Let's get this win!
Whoever it was, I'll find them and kill them!
I found it.
That's yours, isn't it?
So you're the thief!
Are you mocking us?!
I was just nice enough to return it to its owner.
Or would you rather I report the money I found to the police?
W-why did you bring it?
I'm also betting. I love baseball.
That's Michiru Kagemori.
She's definitely shapeshifting into weird forms.
I see. Very interesting.
Game set!
Killer Animals take the win!
I never thought losing would be this painful...!
You did great, Bears!
The losing Bears are being received with a warm applause!
There hasn't been a match like this in Animacity until now, has there?
What a moving final match! A final good game!
Thank you Bears! The stars of the slums, Bears!
This is your reward.
So you follow your instructions next time.
Sorry, but I refuse.
I don't wanna gamble. I wanna play baseball.
I couldn't find any evidence of baseball gambling.
It seems it'll take some time...
...to change this city.
Michiru!
I bought a tool to make us better at baseball thanks to the money we got, with a lifetime payment plan!
Yay!
Come on, you fools!
Return that!
Eh? Why?
Heh... Having fun...?
♪～
～♪