♪～
～♪
Gem!
I told you not to shower while in beast mode, your feathers clog everything up!
Let me shower how I want.
Breaking such a simple promise... Ginrou-sama is watching, you know!
Ginrou-sama...
Michiru, you don't even know about Ginrou-sama?
I just know about him by name...
That won't do! Let me explain.
Depending on the era, humans and beastmen have lived with certain distance between them...
...but no matter the era, beastmen have always gone through a crisis.
That's when a savior appeared...
That's Ginrou-sama.
A worldwide legend saying Ginrou-sama has saved us has existed for as much as a thousand years.
Did you draw this, Mr. Gem?
I'll make a living out of this once I'm old.
Don't mistify her!
Huh? You're leaving?
Hey, are you listening?!
Guess I'll go as well.
Hey, you two.
Here.
You always give this to me, but what is it?
It's a charm for safety, to give to Ginrou-sama in case he comes to your aid.
I see~ Thank you!
Ah! You'll be cursed!
There's no way there's a god that won't save people if you don't give it food.
Everyone believes it, so shouldn't you be more respectful?
That's why you have no friends.
You don't have any, either.
I had many friends.
I also had a very close friend, and she's super cute!
Why so proud?
I mean, it's my pride.
What's your name?
Nazuna!
Even if you read it upside down...!
It's Nazuna!
My dream is your dream!
No matter how you look at it, I'm an idol in every direction!
I'm Nazuna Hiwatashi!
That'll definitely catch on!
Come on, you should audition!
I don't wanna be chosen by anyone.
I'd rather be the one choosing.
Ah, you're scared.
Huh?
We almost died due to a single accident!
Nothing can scare us anymore!
There's a chance in adversity! Come on, you should become a real idol!
H-hey... That's dangerous!
I'm not giving up on basketball...
...so let's make it to the top in our own fields!
We can become anything we want!
Hm... You're amazing, Michiru.
...But one day, right in front of me...
...right in front of me, she was abducted.
...wait, what?
If you're looking for Oogami, he went to the mayor's.
Here.
Huh?
It's this month's phone bill.
So I pay you for that, too?
If ya can't pay it, then earn it.
I'm overpricing this product to sell it to those slum fools.
I hate it... Having to take part in a crime just to pay for my phone.
Michiru!
Jackie!
That's...
Look at this water purifier!
They say it can even turn muddy water into mineral water!
I bought it with a loan!
With a lifetime payment plan!
Hey.
Which one of you is "Jackie"?
I told you lifetime payments were bad!
I mean, when I woke up from the shopping spree dazzle...
It won't really matter even if I just start with you guys...
...but I'll make an example out of you.
Anyone who pushes the paying date even a day will be met with fire from now on.
Jackie! Hey, move it!
Jackie!
Hey, what's that?
Stop at once, lost beastmen.
The hell are you?
Beastmen hurting other beastmen...
That's low even for humans.
What the hell are you blabbering on about?
Those who don't pay up aren't beastmen or humans...
They're trash! Shouldn't you take out the trash?
They are not trash.
We are all noble beastmen.
You must not forget that honor.
Ginrou-sama is watching.
Are you stupid?
Ginrou is just a fairytale made up by weaklings!
Rejoice!
We will show the silver light even to unenlightened beastmen like you!
Silver wolf guru, Déesse Louve!
She has descended into Animacity, the capital of the beastmen!
I don't care if you're a guru or whatever. Stay back!
If you interfere, I'll burn you all as well!
Jackie!
Burn! Burn!
Hot! Hot! It's hot!
My flesh is burning! What a nice smell~
It's Ginrou!
It's Ginrou-sama!
What are you all doing?! Shoot, shoot them!
It's no use! We can't shoot!
Please forgive us!
Get it together, you two!
That's Ginrou...
Ginrou-sama is the god of beastmen!
She will erase your troubles and fears by way of the silver light!
Worship our guardian deity, Ginrou-sama!
Déesse Louve! She is the maiden of Ginrou!
The silver light be with you.
Let's all shine together.
Hold on, that's Nazuna!
Heeeey, Nazuna! Nazuna!
It's me! Look! It's... H-hold on...
What are you doing? H-hold on...!
Even if you read it upside down~?!
Back down.
I feel great evil coming from this animal.
You must not get close until I say otherwise.
Michiru? I knew it was you, Michiru!
Why are you here? To think you also became a beastman...
Nazuna...
Uh, I mean, this is...
Thank god you're alive!
You're okay! Thank god!
Michiru...
A tanuki?
I-I'm a raccoon.
For some reason, I switched a little later...
I've been living here for a while...
Déesse Louve!
Come with me!
Eh? H-hold on!
Is it okay to just leave those guys be?
I guess...
Are you...
Hey.
You're a tanuki! Why'd you say you were a raccoon?
Aah, there's no way you're a raccoon!
I mean, you're a silver wolf, meanwhile I'm just a tanuki...
Hold on a sec.
I'm not a silver wolf. I'm a fox.
A fox? Were you transformed?
Keep it a secret! I'll be in big trouble if anyone finds out.
Okay, got it.
Michiru... Are you maybe unable to return to your human form?
I couldn't at first, but now I can.
Well, but I mean, why are you in beast form?
Come on. Isn't it more convenient to be like this?
I know! Come to my house! I have lots of things to tell you!
You live here?
Yeah!
Really?! Let's go then!
Yeah, let's go!
The Silver Wolf Order.
They're a religious group that serve Ginrou. They search for beastmen freedom and pilgrimage through many countries.
I heard rumors, but to think the guru is actually Ginrou...
A complete beast form...
A normal beastman shouldn't be able to accomplish that.
Are they welcome despite that?
"Any beastman is welcome" is this city's motto.
You don't like it?
I don't.
Yeah. As expected.
I was putting off meeting them to do some research on them...
...but I figure it'd be faster to see them directly.
So you saw me getting abducted?
It was a bit far so I couldn't see well...
...but you disappeared just after that, so I immediately got what happened.
I thought things like "Are they gonna murder me?". It was super scary!
Becoming a beastman in the first place...
...anyone would panic.
Yeah, you're right.
I was taken to some sort of weird research facility...
...and the one who got me out of there was Boris Cliff.
He knew I had transforming abilities.
He had me train, and after that, I joined the Silver Wolf Order.
He made me, who can transform into Ginrou, into a guru...
...and he settled with being my trainer.
Was Boris that masked guy who was with you?
Yep!
Is he trustworthy? Isn't he a bit shady?
He's not shady.
Have you ever seen him without the mask?
Nope.
He's always using that mask? Isn't that kinda gross?
It's not.
I told you, Boris saved me from that facility.
So he's not a bad guy.
I see. I guess that's okay then.
What about you? How long have you been this way?
Just after it happened to you, I think.
I holed up in my house and hid for a while...
...but I wanted to look for a way to go back to normal...
...and I thought I could find something by coming here.
No one knows anything about this disease.
Disease?
I think it's a disease. A beastman disease.
A beastman disease, huh...
You seem to be having a lot of fun, though.
What? Even like this, it's pretty rough!
Looks like you have lots of friends.
Well, there are plenty of bad people here, too.
But there are also people who come and help me out.
I see~
Is that the mayor of Animacity?
Yeah! I help her out sometimes.
Hey!
Let's live here together!
Leave all that guru stuff behind.
I promise I'll find a cure, so before we go back to being human, let's try our best together!
Ah, he's back!
Shirou, welcome home.
Thanks.
Hey, Shirou! Ms. Melissa!
Could you let a friend stay here as well?
A friend?
No way.
What? Why?
That woman can't be here.
I'm going back.
Ah... Wait, Nazuna!
Hold it!
Is that friend of yours... a human?
That's right. Nazuna and I have the same beastman disease.
Why is it okay if I'm here but Nazuna can't?
That cult is fishy. There's definitely something else to it.
You can't trust that woman, either.
What the hell...
How about you kick me out as well?
Excuse me!
I'm Michiru Kagemori!
I want to join!
Boris.
I saw the guru earlier this evening and I was moved by it!
Please!
Alright.
Let Ginrou-sama guide you.
Ugh, what's up with that? So gross.
Welcome, sister.
Here. I'll guide you to your tent.
Ah, understood! Please do!
That mayor is always busy. She is not willing to see us.
Ah, I see.
By the way, a moment ago...
A girl by the name of Kagemori came to join us...
Do you know her?
Who knows.
Be beautiful.
More beautiful than a god.
Boris told me. I can't believe you joined the Silver Wolf Order.
Let's run away together.
That Boris guy's grossness isn't normal!
You can't trust a guy like that!
Michiru, you're pretty dumb.
What?!
Don't raise your voice!
It's best if you return.
Animacity isn't willing to welcome a cult.
It's possible we might just have to leave.
Why?
You're leaving too? Wouldn't you rather stay here?
Unlike you, I have no place to be here.
That guy said I can't be here, didn't he?
That's...
The mayor is also unwilling to meet.
The mayor? You went to see her?
More like she refused to receive me.
You can meet her.
Leave it to me.
I know she's always at a particular store in the morning.
Let's go meet her together.
I'm sure she'll understand if she just talks with you properly.
Let's go before everyone wakes up.
H-hey, hold on!
We're up early tomorrow. Go sleep!
I'm sure it'll be okay. I can be with you like this...
Mayor Rose!
Ms. Michiru.
I brought a person who wanted to see you.
I was a human...!
I am the Silver Wolf Order Guru...
Déesse Louve.
Thank you for making time to meet me.
Today, I am requesting for the permanent residence for the Silver Wolf Order members in Animacity.
Ah... Nazuna?
If that's what you want to talk about...
Why won't you listen to what I have to say?
"Animacity welcomes every beastman".
Is that pledge a lie?
Ginrou is a sacred entity to beastmen.
Playing with its existence is something unforgivable.
This city is open to every beastman.
But we don't need someone who deceives beastmen in this city.
No, that's...!
It's true that I am a human.
I'm not the legendary Ginrou.
As expected.
But does Ginrou exist in the first place?
An immortal wolf beastman living for more than a thousand years...
He's a beastman, but he takes the form of a wolf.
There's no way there's someone like that.
But by having them hold onto that fictitious existence, you can keep beastmen in check.
They were looking for salvation. Am I wrong?
That's why I'm making that lie a reality.
For the sake of beastmen's happiness.
I'm not fabricating hope.
We are instilling hope into them.
Animacity must be needing that very hope.
Isn't that right, Mayor Rose Barbarei?
Nazuna...
Your friend is very interesting.
Come to the city hall this afternoon. We'll begin the settlement procedures.
Understood.
Hmm! What a nice morning~
I'm hungry.
Come on...
What?
I should be the one saying "what"! You deceived me! What's with that attitude?!
I deceived you?
I mean, I thought you were overworking yourself as a guru, so I pitied you and thought about helping you.
So what was that just now?
Did you plan to use me?
Scary!
What?
You become sharp-tongued as soon as things don't go exactly how you thought.
I would've been fine even if I didn't rely on you.
You even looked so smug when you had me meet the mayor~
You said you weren't able to meet the mayor...
You think the mayor acknowledged me because I relied on you?
There's no way!
It was decided way before all of this!
I'm sure she investigated our cult, either way.
That's why, even if you weren't involved...
...the result would've been more or less the same.
Then why did you ask me to do it?
I didn't ask you to.
You did what you wanted based on your assumptions from the start.
Assumptions?
I didn't even say anything about quitting my guru status in the first place, did I?
See? You don't get it.
I don't even want to quit. I'm finally an idol.
An idol?
Being a guru is like being an idol!
So many beastmen worship me, praise me...
They look for hope and dreams in me!
Isn't that like being an idol?
What the hell...
Are you okay with being used as an idol by that gross grandpa?
Besides, saying a guru is an idol...
You haven't changed a bit, Michiru.
When something happens right before your eyes, you jump into it without a second thought.
That part of you hasn't changed at all.
Jumping in based on assumptions...
...deciding to pity someone all by yourself...
...and thinking about saving someone just like that...
Isn't that just to stroke your ego?
That's not...
Also, Boris isn't as gross as you think.
That's not true.
See, you're pushing it.
I decided to do anything to achieve my dreams.
I'm not Nazuna right now.
I'm the Silver Wolf Maiden, Déesse Louve!
Okay... I got it.
That's enough then.
However!
I have no friend named Déesse-whatever!
♪～
～♪
Why...?