♪～
～♪
To the beastman in flight...
...you are invading Japanese airspace without permission.
Please land and fill the required entry paperwork immediately.
I'm a wandering albatross.
That should be covered by the International Migratory Bird Convention...
Beastmen don't fall under the Migratory Convention.
If you continue to fly, we will consider this an airspace violation and attack accordingly.
No sense of humor, huh...
Civil workers are pretty strict...
Pushing your own "justice" onto others and pitying them...
...and deciding to "help them out"...
...isn't that just to stroke your own ego?
We were finally reunited, so why...?
Damn it!
This is like The Spirit of St. Louis...
...but this storm is a little rough.
I'm trying my best...
What's she mean with "pushing it"?
What...?
Damn... What a screw-up.
Oh! You're awake?
Oh, was that my doing?
Yeah! You made quite a nice hole.
You should go back to bed.
I mean, I caused this whole mess...
...so I can't really sleep.
Looks like you're fine.
Be careful, girl.
A gust of wind is coming.
Michiru!
Heh, warm food really is the best.
Been long since you last had any?
I'm always up in the sky.
Are you also here in Animacity to take refuge?
We should get you registered, then.
I'm not staying for long. I'm a wandering albatross, after all.
Wandering? Are you migrating?
Yeah.
I'm jealous...
Of what?
You can fly, right? And you can go anywhere.
If I was able to fly, it would've been easier for me to get here.
You wanna fly, girl?
What? Oh, yeah!
I looked up the Silver Wolf Order.
It used to be a private religion of sorts up until half a year ago...
...but it grew exponentially and gained more power as soon as Boris Cliff joined.
And their guru seems to be an old friend of that tanuki girl.
They both have this "beastman disease", and they're close friends.
That can't be a coincidence... right?
Did they infect one another?
If that were the case, the disease would've spread more.
That's true.
The mystery just keeps on growing.
I'll let the cult stay for now.
If they're infected, it's best to keep them under observation.
Mayor, you have a visitor.
I don't have anything in my schedule.
That's...
Apologies for the sudden visit.
It's been a while, Mayor Rose Barbarei.
President Alan. To think you'd humble me with a visit...
I'm sorry. I visited on a whim.
I'm Alan Sylvasta.
The boss of Sylvasta Pharmaceutics. Nice to meet you.
I'm Shirou Oogami.
Do you dislike handshakes?
Yeah. I don't want human smell on me.
I see. My apologies.
Mr. Oogami is the Mayor's advisor.
He's been helping ever since Animacity was established.
That means we're in the same position.
I fund the city, and you use your intelligence.
Thank you for your work in Sylvasta Pharmaceutics' bomb incident.
You knew about that...
You and that cute assistant of yours exposed the foolish crimes of Mr. Yaba and his companions.
I got the reports about it.
Cute assistant?
Am I wrong? I mean that tanuki girl.
She's not cute.
Hahaha... I'm just being polite. Don't take it too seriously.
I'm sorry for coming here uninvited.
It seems you want that Silver Wolf Order to stay here.
It's best if you drop that.
If we do that, the whole purpose of this city collapses.
That's true.
Animacity is meant to be a refuge for oppressed beastmen.
By living here, they get used to the human way of living...
...and learn how to behave in order to coexist with humans.
I resonated with that, so as the human representative, I chose to give you financial aid.
That's right. Animacity rejects no beastmen.
So why?
Heheh... a whim, perhaps?
Wow, those are some nice fangs! As expected of a wolf beastman.
Oogami!
I'm sure the successor of the Sylvasta Conglomerate...
...isn't someone who would act on a whim.
You think too highly of me.
I just think the Silver Wolf Order isn't needed in Animacity.
Why?
Beastmen continue to modernize themselves...
...so inviting a beastman cult would have an adverse effect, wouldn't it?
It would encourage anti-beastmen.
Did you know?
The Parliament, the members of anti-beastmen movements, journalists...
Lately, the leaders of beastmen rights movements
have been getting attacked at every opportunity by them.
There's also info on an unidentified flying beastman trespassing.
Of course, the decision making is up to you.
Depending on your decision, I might need to change my opinion.
Is that a threat?
It's a warning.
I'll be in charge of looking over the chief-less Medical Center from now on.
I'd like to keep trusting you with Animacity like I have until now.
Farewell.
This feels great! Whoa!
The wind in this city is very peculiar.
Gotcha!
Whoa! That's amazing!
How do you "catch the wind"?
How? You just know after getting used to it.
Where the wind starts and where it wants to go...
I learned that from my father. And my father, from my grandfather, and so on.
Technically, it's down to humidity or pressure in the air...
Well, there are a few complications...
...but a beastman's body remembers.
Must be nice being so free...
Free... Well, it used to be like that.
We're albatross beastmen. Like regular albatrosses, we migrate.
We've been doing that for generations.
When beastmen started having the same rights as humans...
...migrating was prohibited.
You need a proper passport to cross national borders...
...and need to go through proper migration procedures.
I see...
It's the route my ancestors had to fly through.
It's rooted deep within our bodies.
We can't change that now.
"Why do we have to accommodate to humans' convenience?"
We had friends who said that and flew either way, only to be shot down.
Saying it was "trespassing".
That's terrible...
Beastmen are bound by the rules of humanity.
Are humans really all that...?
Could I have one of those?
These are made for beastmen.
Ah, can you tell I'm a human?
By the smell.
Is that so? Oh well. Just give me one.
Here you go.
Yeah. I really can't drink this.
Are you really going with what that kid said?
Don't underestimate him just because he's young.
The Sylvasta Conglomerate has been prestigious in Europe for generations.
They're looking to make Alan their leader.
You know the source of income for this city comes directly  from Sylvasta Pharmaceutics' financial aid, don't you?
That cult is fishy.
But I dislike the idea of following a human's orders even more.
We have to make a decision either way.
Even if it results...
...in making enemies among beastmen.
We have confirmation from the government.
It seems they've lost track of the bird beastman who trespassed into Animacity.
They say it's likely he's a terrorist who opposes the beastmen rights movement.
It seems what Alan said wasn't just a threat after all.
What's that fool doing?
Alright, the sightseeing flight is over, girl.
Here. Sorry, they're dollars...
...but this is to pay for the roof.
I'll probably be gone by tomorrow. This is goodbye.
You're leaving already?
Well, I'm an albatross.
You're right.
At least tell me your name.
Pinga.
See ya, Mr. Pinga! If you come to the city again, make sure to stop by!
Where's that bird beastman?
Oh, you mean Pinga?
He left.
What?
He might be a terrorist.
Terrorist? No way~
He said he'll leave the city tomorrow.
Then he might do something tonight.
What's with you?
I'm telling you he's not like that.
Are you sure about that? You just flew together for a bit.
Don't say it like that...
I mean... why do you know we went flying?
I saw you both recklessly flying around from the town hall.
It wasn't reckless! Not at all.
You just don't get it.
What?
I didn't know...
I didn't know beastmen weren't happy even if they have their rights.
Albatross problems...
You knew about this?
Pinga said he even had friends who were shot down.
They must've had their reasons.
C'mon... Why do you always assume the worst?
It seems anti-beastmen terrorist groups are forming in Animacity.
They're bird beastmen, too.
This timing can't be a coincidence.
There's also no time to argue about it.
We should find him and clear any suspicions then, right?
If we can clear them.
Can't you find him by smell?
The sky is my weak point. All remaining smell must've dissipated by now.
Is there any other way?
Even if there isn't, he's a target.
Wait!
The Silver Wolf Order was looking to settle in Animacity, but Mayor Rose refused their request.
She is preparing an alternate refuge, and is currently negotiating.
The mayor is saying "we don't have the required infrastructure to usher them in"...
...and "we will temporarily relocate them, but we are making preparations to bring them into our city soon".
Is this alright?
Yes. Everything is going according to plan.
Hey! The cult is moving!
What? Seriously?
Yeah. Ginrou-sama is leading them.
Ginrou-sama?
We, the Silver Wolf Order, wished to settle in Animacity.
However, Mayor Rose refused our wish.
This is due to concerns from Sylvasta Pharmaceutics.
However, we are not the fanatics they think we are.
We only wish for a paradise for beastmen.
Let us pray! To dissipate any and all misunderstandings!
Rejoice!
Ginrou is an entity who protects beastmen.
Her light will bring about eternal calm to all beastmen!
The cult is right in front of the Medical Center.
It seems they noticed President Alan's interference.
This isn't a message from the gods... is it?
A lot of people saw him come into the Town Hall.
In any case, contact the police.
Just to take a look at the situation. No violence.
Alright, let's go.
What are you doing?!
Terrorists in Animacity are unforgivable!
I'd love it if you didn't get in my way.
Shirou!
Damn it, if I could just fly...!
Don't think badly of me!
Agh, I...
want... to...!
You can fly?!
This is a first for me!
A first?!
Yeah!
Can you catch up to him?
Leave it to me!
Hold on! Is that even possible?
You won't get away this time.
You're the tanuki girl.
Was I being fooled?
You're an ex-soldier, aren't you?
Yeah, I used to be in the military when I was young.
I believed in beastmen rights and fought against anti-beastmen extremists.
To think that would result in being unable to fly...
...without thinking of the consequences...
And that's why...
That's why you think being a terrorist is okay?
Did you really plan on attacking the Mayor?
The bomb was a bluff.
It isn't lethal at all.
I had that as a threat so they would listen to me.
Government officials wouldn't listen to me, either way.
So? What will you do?
I just want to protect this city.
Go.
Right now.
You haven't done anything yet.
Girl...
These are my comrades who were caught up in the conflict for beastmen rights and died.
If this is a beastman city, then I want to make tombs for them here.
Please tell that to the Mayor.
Yeah.
I'll tell her. I promise.
Oh, right. I wasn't the only one flying to this city.
There's someone else.
There's only one beastman I know who could go that fast.
In the "dark-side", we call him "Meteor".
He's a hitman who will do anything for money. Be careful.
Is he targeting the Mayor?
No. If that was the case, I would know about it.
That means...
President, going out is dangerous!
Don't worry. Running and hiding would just make things worse.
Are we too late?
What is that?
Can you fly again?
Look! Look at Ginrou and her wings!
Her grace befalls not only beastmen, but humans far and wide as well!
Our founder, Ms. Déesse Louve, is just...
the one who will save the world of beastmen!
You failed. Give it up.
Listen! Listen to the voices of the citizen!
Can you disregard these voices, Alan Sylvasta?
Damn, I'm done for.
Amazing...
You're amazing, Nazuna.
♪～
～♪