Yes, it's about whether we should allow the cult to stay.
Well, we have no choice.
After the uproar from the public...
...if we don't accept the cult, a riot will be inevitable.
I was saved by them myself.
There's no reason to oppose them.
However... the amount of people who showed up was unexpected.
Around 5,000 people were confirmed to be there.
They're distributed all over Animacity.
Must be rough for you.
Well, hang in there.
What's the situation?
The Beast Factor deactivator has stabilized.
Just one more step.
Good. Keep it up.
Shall we make one final verification?
♪～
～♪
Leader!
Guru!
It's barely been 3 days since the cult moved into that building...
That's Ginrou-sama for you.
The power of faith is strong, as they say.
Nazuna!
Would you look at that, you can fly too.
Were you hiding it?
No! Yesterday was a first for me.
You're the one who didn't tell me you could fly.
Do I have to tell you everything?
That's not what...
Whatever!
I can't believe you moved right in front of me.
Huh? Boris decided that by himself.
Aside from that, don't tell anyone about my identity.
The fact I'm a human must stay a secret.
I told you I'm not gonna tell anyone.
But I mean, Nazuna, are you...
...are you okay with this?
I'm not Nazuna.
Déesse Louve.
I'm not Nazuna. I'm Ms. Déesse Louve.
What language is that? I can't remember that...
Where did you go?
To Nazuna's... though she's "not Nazuna" now, apparently.
Did you go see her?
I just stumbled upon her.
Why? Is that bad?
No.
Uhm... can I help you?
I have an investigation on a falcon beastman we caught.
Are you coming?
I think you'd want to know who made the request.
Are you inviting me?
Yeah.
Really?
It's okay if you don't want to.
I do! I'm coming!
Must be a tough task to teach a sinner.
Sinners are the exact people who need to be taught by God.
That much is obvious.
He was the chief for the Medical Center...
He was caught in an embezzlement.
I don't think he'll misbehave, but be careful.
I don't believe in Ginrou.
So that's the kind of person you are.
Have I seen you before?
You can't tell now, can you? Not with this form.
What?
Let's expose your sin.
I assume you planned on getting away with it...
...but if the truth came out, President Alan wouldn't just let it slide, would he?
Y-you...
Who are you?
That's...
The trainer from the cult.
Ya-Yaba, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Oh, Michiru's here, too?
Have you gotten used to this city?
Yeah, I guess...
Oh, you're slurring a bit.
Inspector! Yaba is breaking out!
That's Yaba?!
He's completely different from before!
Yeah.
You have permission to fire! Do it! Do it!
Damn it... Why is he so out of control?!
I'll stop him.
What?
The building is on fire...
Yes. The outbreak is in progress. The hypothesis is correct.
I won't let you rage any more!
Seize him at any cost!
He broke through the fence!
At this rate, he'll make it to the city!
What?!
Shirou!
It's okay, this is nothing...
But, your arm...!
It fixed itself!
Oogami having this much trouble, though...
If that thing makes it to the city... we'll be in big trouble!
What are you doing?!
I'll take care of this!
I'll take him somewhere with...
...no people...!
Don't be stupid! Just run!
Shut up!
Don't think you can do everything alone!
I'll help whenever I can...!
If that's the case... Show me!
Put more force into it!
More force... Then...
...bigger wings!
T-they picked it up!
Stop moving!
You damn...!
To the wharf!
There shouldn't be any people there!
Got it!
You're moving again...!
Drop him!
At this height?!
I don't care, hurry! I'll be fine!
Got it!
We did it!
Somehow...
...! Get down!
Sh... Shirou...
Ngh... I'm fine... Run...
S-Shirou!
I'm fine...
You can't say that with such a wound! We should run!
We can't leave that guy like that...
That's my responsibility.
S... S... Stop it!
Run...!
I did it!
Shirou, run!
There's no other way...
Ginrou...?
I mean... Shirou?!
Stay back.
Shirou!
A-an ambulance!
Stop it.
I'll... be alright...
Oogami!
Mayor! Why are you here?
Inspector Tachiki called me.
Uh... Shirou is...!
He will be okay.
Take him to the car.
Understood.
She found out...
I see...
He finally calmed down...
The wound is closing, so he's gonna be fine.
That wasn't just a wound...
He's really immortal, huh.
I'm glad you didn't get any major wounds.
It's thanks to Shirou.
Who... What is he?
Shirou is Ginrou?
That's your friend, isn't she?
Don't play dumb, please. I heard Shirou mutter "She found out" just earlier.
Nazuna is a fake Ginrou. You know that, don't you?
Correct.
Is Shirou the real Ginrou?
What will you do with that information?
I... I don't know anything about Shirou.
I never tried to know him, either.
It's probably already decided that Shirou and I are different...
Because he's a beastman and you're a human?
I somehow felt like I could hate Shirou...
...because he hates humans.
That sort of prejudice is...
...But I'm exactly the same.
...I thought Shirou and I were different because he's a beastman...
When I turned into a beastman, I was scared.
That's probably because I didn't know anything about beastmen.
That's why... I wanna know more about Shirou.
Alright.
A Ginrou with wings, huh...
That's very godly indeed.
But that's just to make the imitation look more gaudy and appealing.
Imitation?
Shirou Oogami is the real Ginrou.
For the last thousand years.
T-thousand years?!
Has he been living for a thousand years then?!
Correct.
He doesn't look that old, though...
At first sight, at least.
Apparently he stopped aging as soon as he became Ginrou.
He became Ginrou?
It's not like Oogami was Ginrou since the beginning.
It's a long story.
About a thousand years ago, in the very east of Europe...
There was a city called Nirvasyl.
It was a beastmen-only city...
...like our city, Animacity.
He was living there, like a regular wolf beastman.
At the time, beastmen and humans had trades...
...and friendly relationships even between them.
But one day...
...suddenly, without any warning...
...the human military attacked Nirvasyl.
His own kind was slaughtered...
...and he himself was slain, too...
His body was thrown away like countless others...
...and left to rot.
At that moment, something peculiar happened.
There's no clear reason as to why it happened.
But the blood of all 2,000 Nirvasyl brethren was...
...what gave him an immortal body.
He believes so, as well.
That's...
He obtained the power of Ginrou...
...he went in search for the general who killed his kind...
...and in his search, he killed countless human soldiers.
However, he couldn't find the general he was looking for.
When he felt the emptiness left by revenge...
...that's when he became the protector of beastmen.
Sometimes protecting them from human oppression...
...and sometimes being the guide for the new world.
And that became the legend of Ginrou...
When we first met...
...was around the final years of World War II.
Wanting to see if they could turn beastmen into biological weapons...
...countries like that existed as well.
In those countries, beastmen were captured and put in concentration camps...
...and were repeatedly experimented with.
That's when we were saved by Ginrou.
But when he saw the disaster resulting from the experiments beastmen were put through...
...he slaughtered all humans in the research facility.
From then on, he's never once changed into his Ginrou form.
He's afraid of his own power, so he keeps Ginrou sealed away.
So please don't tell anyone he's Ginrou. Do you understand?
I don't get it.
I don't really get it.
So I'll just keep things as they are.
To me, he's Shirou Oogami.
That cold and unfriendly person who desperately fights to protect Animacity.
Hehe. Right. That's okay.
No... That's perfect.
Yeah.
Since I survived, I aimed to become a scientist.
I figured humans couldn't be the only ones to know about beastmen. Beastmen should know, too.
This little guy was at that lab, too.
He's a crow who got his body reconstructed.
That's why he's been living for so long.
He was saved along with me.
Uhm... I'll keep it quiet.
I'll keep the fact that Shirou is Ginrou to myself.
But...
...the fact that Ginrou is actually real...
...I have someone I want to tell that to.
Please.
What would he say...?
I don't mind.
Shirou!
Go.
Yeah!
Are you sure?
If we stopped her, she'd talk either way.
Heh. Seems like you're starting to understand her.
She's really good at manipulating me.
I'll go, too. I have something I'm interested in.
Michiru...
Well, if it isn't the Mayor.
Show me the scan data.
B-but...
I don't mind.
Ah, but...
You know, don't you? Before she became the Mayor...
...she was the first person ever to research the Beast Factor.
She was the first beastman to get a PhD.
W-what's this shift in the Beast Factor?!
That's right. We're investigating that as well.
I trust you'll contact me as soon as there is any progress?
With pleasure.
Having the top of Sylvasta Pharmaceutics here is reassuring.
If anything happens, I trust you'll handle it immediately.
That is why I'm here.
That's right. That's exactly why.
♪～
～♪