♪～
～♪
Why don't you stop this "guru" thing?
You're not Ginrou.
You have no need to keep the lie up like that.
Because the real Ginrou is out there.
So what?
I'm the Silver Wolf Maiden, "Déesse Louve".
The order's "fanclub" is close to surpassing 5,000 members.
Their lives are full of sorrow, but just by looking at me, they feel a little better.
Déesse Louve serves as a ray of hope for those people.
I mean, Michiru, why did you come here to tell me that?
Did you come to accuse me of being a fake?
No! I just...
Oh, you're "worried about me"?
And there's that "justice" of yours rearing its head!
I've made up my mind a long time ago.
Staying up late is bad for the skin, so hurry up and leave.
Shirou. How are your wounds?
You came here to talk, right?
Yeah...
No one knows about your secret, so don't worry.
When you're hungry, it's easy to feel down.
You have to see things, feel things for yourself...
...and find an asnwer that convinces you.
What?
It's nothing.
I was thinking how a thousand-year-old person is so different...
Are you making fun of me?
Hehe~
Thanks.
I'm digging in.
I'm about to go to the police to look into Yaba. What about you?
I'm good today. I have something planned.
Don't go near the cult. Or the Medical Center. Got it?
I know, I know. See you later!
The slums!
It should've ended up around here...
Michiru!
Whatcha up to?
I should be the one asking that.
What's all this?
Mineral-ish Water!
Using the water purifier I bought recently...
You're still using that?
I do this and... here!
Done! That's Mineral-ish Water!
Aaahhh! Trash-free water is amazing!
Wanna take a sip?
I'll pass.
I sell them for 10 yen each!
It's great! I'll get rich in no time!
There it is!
Oh! That's the Ginrou-sama thing!
I love the Silver Wolf Maiden!
I've been changing thanks to Ginrou-sama!
I don't do things like pulling other people's flowers out...
...or pull out other people's bicycle saddles and resell them anymore!
Because Ginrou-sama is watching!
Everyone in the slums says that.
May you become a good beastman!
Is that okay, then?
T-this is Mineral-ish Water!
-ish! I'm not lying!
It's business! Business!
If "good beastmen" hear about this, they'll be disgusted.
Do you also like Ginrou-sama?
Yeah... I like her.
I found a 10-yen coin!
I gotta show it to everyone!
He hasn't changed a bit...
Before Yaba went out of control, there wasn't anything peculiar about him.
That day, Yaba was acting like normal...
...and Boris, the trainer for the cult came to visit...
Boris?
He said something about "teaching sinners about God".
The jail was completely obliterated, and dangerous criminals broke out.
No matter how many reports I make, it'll never be enough.
I'd like to see Yaba's body.
Ah, it was transported to the Medical Center.
To the Medical Center? The autopsy is a job for the police.
Obeying orders from above is also a job for the police.
Nazuna?
Nazuna!
The Medical Center?
How are the results for that scan going?
Ah, about that...
Nazuna!
Nazuna! Nazuna!
Michiru?!
Aaahhh... Are you okay?
What are you doing?!
Entry is prohibited to unrelated parties!
Nazuna and I are plenty related!
Michiru, no!
Don't touch Nazuna!
This damn brute...!
Michiru... That's enough...
Michiru!
Release her.
What do you plan to do with Nazuna?!
If anything happens to Nazuna...
The cult will hear about it!
And I... I will...!
That habit of yours of being stubborn and jumping in...
You don't change at all, huh.
My apologies.
I'm sure she mistook this as me being abducted.
It's alright. Wanting to save your friend and acting recklessly because of that...
I can't say I disapprove.
Nazuna, you've got quite the friend.
You're Michiru, right? I've heard a lot about you from Nazuna.
I know you.
You're that admirable Sylvasta guy...
Oh, what an honor.
That's right. I am Alan Sylvasta.
I'm the representative of Sylvasta Pharmaceutics.
What's going on? Why is Nazuna here?
I just came to take an MRI scan.
MRI?
She's been undergoing regular check-ups for a while...
...and letting us get some data out of it.
I'm here on my own volition.
Would you go home?
Well, since this is a peculiar occasion...
...we should let Michiru here into the loop as well.
That's...
Leaving her in the dark with half-baked details could cause a lot of trouble for us in the future...
I think Michiru has the right to know.
About how she became a beastman...
Alright.
Nazuna?
Michiru, I ought to apologize to you.
The reason behind your beast form... is this Medical Center.
You were both accidentally transfused a Beast Factor reagent extracted from a beastman.
In the drugs Yaiba and Mimura were trafficking...
The Beast Factor reagent was mixed in by accident.
Those were accidentally administered to both of you.
That's...
Yaba noticed the amount of packages didn't line up, so he desperately tried to track it down.
As a result, he found out that Nazuna could transform into a beastman...
...and quickly abducted and isolated her.
But he only noticed you could also transform into a beastman...
...after you came to the city.
The real reason behind the bombing was so they could erase all data about the mixup.
Because the development of the reagent was top secret.
If it were discovered, no punishment for letting that slip would be enough.
If only you weren't here...!
Are you saying Nazuna and I are victims of your research?
That's horrible!
My apologies...
We're fully responsible for this.
But it's alright. You can go back to being human.
We're developing a cure for the "beastman disease". It will be completed soon.
If you use that, you and Nazuna will be able to go back to normal.
That's why I'm here to help Sylvasta.
When I heard I was made into a beastman, I was shocked.
But Sylvasta Pharmaceutics took all responsibility...
...and they promised to make a cure for me to return to normal.
Until the cure is completed, I assigned a job...
...to Nazuna, to instill hope into all beastmen.
By transforming, that is.
Hold on! Didn't you oppose the cult coming to Animacity in the first place?
Yeah. I needed to do that.
To decrease beastmen's mental entropy...
...the Silver Wolf Order is needed.
E... Entropy...?
Haven't you noticed since moving to Animacity?
Beastmen are easily driven by their emotions.
Their frustration builds up and they explode from little things, disturbing the peace.
To preserve their mental stability, we're using their faith in Ginrou.
Facing a "god" makes their mental entropy decrease.
Is that different from stress?
However, being invited by religions created by the very humans who oppress beastmen... They won't believe in that.
What about that?
You were targeted but Nazuna saved you, didn't she?
I had prior information that indicated I might be targeted.
I just used that to my advantage.
We must put up a show in order for people to believe, after all.
Having beastmen choose to believe on their own...
...would lead to their mental entropy quickly decreasing.
So it's stress...
Mental entropy... Do you understand?
You were fooling everyone?
It was a show!
It's resulting in a more orderly Animacity.
It would've been nice to know all this.
I told you I'm looking for a way to cure this disease, didn't I?
You know it's top-secret.
Only Boris and I know about this... There's no way we could've told an outsider like you, Michiru.
The ones with this illness are you and me, Nazuna!
Wouldn't that make that gross geezer an outsider?
I told you he's not gross.
He's around you 24/7, of course he's gross!
Well, calm down.
You're judging people based on appearances.
That applies to both of you.
You saw Nazuna getting pulled into my car...
...and assumed she was being abducted.
But the truth was different, wasn't it?
The truth lies in that which you cannot see.
I'm taking responsibility and developing a cure.
You can both return to your human selves. I promise.
Until then, would you help Nazuna out?
"Help"? What can I do?
He means not to interfere in our business.
"our"...
I told you not to approach the cult or the Medical Center.
They said I can go back to being human.
So it was a medical error?
Yeah.
But he apologized a lot...
...and he promised to develop a cure.
Do you trust that?
He's using you for his own benefit.
You think that just because Alan is human, right?
You distrust anything a human says, after all.
Your friend is a human too, right?
She pretends she's Ginrou and tries to fool beastmen.
That's how humans are.
That's not true! Nazuna isn't like that.
She's lying about being Ginrou...
...but she always said she wanted to be an idol.
She wants to become an idol and have people fawn over her.
Well, there have been situations like that, but...
...she really wants oppressed and sorrowful beastmen to have some hopes and dreams.
That's why she works so hard as Ginrou.
I think that's amazing.
So I want you to overlook the fact that she's pretending to be Ginrou.
Did you enter their cult?
Ah, no way. I can't believe in a counterfeit religion.
But I believe in Nazuna.
I think she noticed that feeling hasn't wavered at all, after all this time.
Though the person in question won't ever say it out loud.
Do you want to be a human again?
Yeah, I want to.
Once you go back, are you leaving Animacity?
I came to love this city...
...but I do want to go back home.
I see.
Yeah.
Leave it open.
The wind is cold tonight. You will catch a cold.
It's fine.
That tanuki girl...
...will she finally stop coming?
Boris.
Yes.
From now on, I'll leave my management to someone else.
Eh...! Why is that?
Because you're gross.
G... Gro...
Also, entering my room without permission...
...that's gross, so stop doing it.
May you become a good beastman.
May... you become a good beastman.
She's a human, after all...
Did you say someting?
No.
What will it be today?
I want to know the results from Yaba's autopsy.
Why did he turn out like that?
I saw a change in his Beast Factor.
Beast Factor?
I don't know the details yet, but...
Once I know, I'll have a report made.
Why in the Medical Center...
It's frustrating, but the Medical Center has cutting edge technology.
Aside from that, Alan isn't as bad of a human as you think he is.
So everyone's siding with him now?
I haven't met a single good human in my entire life.
What? You're always meeting someone like that.
Isn't Michiru a good human?
Thank you for making time in your tight schedule.
What's the urgent business?
Animacity wouldn't have been established had it not been for your efforts.
Prime Minister Shiramizu.
That's why I have some advice.
Advice?
I have something I want to lend to the Japanese government.
♪～
～♪