♪～
～♪
Are you kidding me, Mari?!
This cigar set I bought from you...
...more than half of it is filled with carrots!
No matter how much of a horse you think I am...
...carrots ain't a replacement for cigars!
Give me my money back!
C'mon, I showed you the photo, didn't I?
Asking if this was okay.
You looked at this and agreed!
I'm not foolin' you or anything.
If you get it, drop that horse face of yours and go home.
See ya.
What's with that...
What's wrong, Mari?
I don't know! He just went out of control.
I'll leave this to you!
I'm running away like a hare! (I'm a mink though!)
Shirou, that's...!
The same that happened to Yaba.
Then...
Now!
Got it!
Mayor! There's a rampaging beastman in the city...
Oogami is dealing with it accordingly.
Understood, I'll go as well.
President Alan? I'm sorry, I'm a bit busy...
I'm aware of it...
...and we need to talk.
Can you deal with this...?
Yeah. I won't kill him this time.
We did it!
What's all this?
Shirou!
I'm okay.
We're going after them.
The Medical Center?
They're definitely here.
It'll be dangerous from now on. You should go back...
Hey! You should listen when...
I can't accept you getting shot all the time...
...and I wanna know what all that was.
Besides, you're on edge.
You get worked up as soon as it's about Sylvasta.
Letting you go in alone is much more dangerous.
Let's go. I've been here before, so I know how to sneak in.
Didn't you know how to sneak in?
Oogami.
This is a medical facility. Would you refrain from acting violently?
Alan?
Hello, Michiru.
Perfect timing. I have to ask you something.
Of course.
You guys. Lead the way.
I didn't know they had this kind of facilities here.
It's odd.
What is?
There are only humans here.
This Medical Center should be beastmen-centered.
Is it the smell?
Yeah.
I was going to recover the body in secret, but...
...I didn't know you were taking care of it.
So those machines are the Medical Center's?
What are those anyways?
Those are Engel Machines.
It's medical equipment to protect beastmen.
Medical equipment?
She was shot, you know.
My apologies for that.
They're meant to be used on rampaging beastmen.
We tranquilized that horse beastman to protect him, too.
They probably mistook Michiru for a target.
That was live ammo.
They were quickly dispatched by a subordinate when I was absent, so that was an equipment mistake.
I deeply apologize.
I will make sure this doesn't happen again.
The rampaging beastman is being treated here.
More live experiments?
That is unforgivable in Animacity.
Judging by your reply, you're ready to tear me apart.
That's the plan.
Shirou! Calm down!
What are you trying to do in this city?
You won't talk your way out of this one.
Alright. It'd be better if I explained everything to you.
We need samples from rampaging beastmen.
I know this is rough, but there's no time.
Administer the prototype.
What are you doing?!
Could you pull back those teeth and claws for a moment?
I can't have you recklessly clawing at my throat.
If things stay like they are, Animacity will be destroyed.
Like Nirvasyl.
You know about that city...?
The general leading the soldiers back then...
...was Raymond Sylvasta.
Sylvasta...
That's right.
My ancestor.
Stop it. Do you plan on letting rage consume you and get Michiru involved?
You bastard!
I just want you to listen to me calmly.
Oogami, you misunderstand.
It wasn't the humans who targeted beastmen in Nirvasyl.
It's the opposite. Humans were targeted by beastmen and they protected themselves.
When the human military arrived, the beastmen were already killing each other!
That's ridiculous!
Why do you think humans defeated the beastmen?
This was a thousand years ago. There were no guns or explosives!
With dull blades, heavy shields and arrows...
Does that compare to the attacks of agile beastmen?
Beastmen were fighting and hurting each other...
...the humans just laid the final blow.
Don't talk like you were there!
Then I'll ask you since you were there.
Aren't you reminded of something? I know you are a Nirvasyl survivor.
...! Why do you...?
I've looked into you before.
That's not all.
The story of a silver wolf looking for revenge has been passed down for generations, too.
You gave up on that meaningless revenge, so you should know.
Did humans really slaughter beastmen back then?
Did beastmen really not target each other?
Like Yaba did in a blind rage?
That's... But...
Originally, beastmen of the same kind were living scattered all around.
They weren't used to living with different beastmen.
The stress of having your own territory invaded by other species...
...unconsciously built up.
Having that sort of mental shock in that state...
...activated a "switch" that overloaded their Beast Factor, and their violent instincts amassed.
That's the Beast Factor Breakout Syndrome...
...the "Nirvasyl Syndrome".
I've analyzed the Beast Factor of the beastmen of this city.
Their intracerebral aggressiveness values are rapidly increasing.
If the beastmen population keeps increasing, they'll go overboard.
I see, that's why you had the cult move...
What about the Mayor? Does she know about this?
Of course, I talked to her. She agrees.
A place where beastmen can live rightfully...
A peaceful world to live in...
That's all I wished to create with this city, but...
...was that all wrong?
Have I been creating a beastman hell for the past 10 years?
Are you agreeing with President Alan...?
I checked the data from Sylvasta.
There are no flaws in Alan's theory.
Contact Prime Minister Shiramizu immediately.
Understood.
The reason behind the creation of this Medical Center in Animacity...
...is to create a vaccine for the Nirvasyl Syndrome.
Because I can easily take samples from beastmen.
Wait. The vaccine you're trying to create is...
That's right. A vaccine to turn beastmen into humans.
"Beast Factor Termination Vaccine". If we stop beastmen from transforming, the Nirvasyl Syndrome will not happen.
That's the cure for my beastman disease?
That's right.
No...
So you're making beastmen reject the fact they're beastmen?!
You filthy human!
Shirou!
They're tranquilizers. Please calm down a bit.
All humans... are the same...
They all use brute force to control beastmen...
If this keeps up, beastmen will start killing each other!
Are you okay with that?!
Humans have no right... to decide that!
Shirou!
That's surprising. Even that amount didn't work?
Starting Beast Factor Termination process.
Alright. It's a success!
Stop that! Stop!
Why are you stopping me?!
I won't let humans create a drug to erase beastmen!
You saw it, didn't you?!
This guy and Yaba both rampaged!
Are you okay with everyone rampaging? Are you okay with slaughter?!
Shut up! They'll be turned into humans! By humans!
How about staying alive?!
If you destroy this, you'll be destroying everyone's chance of survival!
Move!
I'm not moving!
Do you want a drug to make you human that badly?!
You just want to go back to being human.
That's not...
You're a human after all.
There's no way you'd get how a beastman feels!
You're always like this! Deciding everything based on that!
There's no way I can understand the feelings of the legendary Ginrou!
Is living a thousand years really all that?
Haven't you just held a grudge against humans for the past thousand years?
W... What did you say?!
Don't move.
Mr. Tachiki...
I received a report about a suspect rampaging at the Medical Center...
...but I can't believe it's you, Oogami.
It's a shame, but...
...he's the one who destroyed all this.
Oogami. Would you come to the station?
You're committing a damage to property crime.
Do you think you can catch me that easily?
I'm begging you to make it easy.
I don't want to be your enemy, but this is my duty.
If you turn on the police as well, you're just a criminal.
You'll be the same as those terrorists.
Shirou...
Let's go after him.
It's best if we let the police handle this.
But...
It's okay. He's a strong man.
Once he calms down, I'm sure he'll understand.
Michiru, thank you.
You protected the vaccine machinery from him, did you not?
It's the same as you saving the lives of many beastmen.
You don't really need to thank me...
Oh, right. Michiru.
I want you to give some advice to Nazuna.
Nazuna?
Yeah.
I entrusted her with a task as well, but...
...I think she'll need your help.
What's the task?
It's something to help Animacity.
To think you'd come get me.
The Mayor has something to tell you.
Figures.
The Town Hall is being guarded by the police. Come with me.
Thank goodness!
See? Michiru came back home!
Yeah.
I've been praying to Ginrou-sama.
The police came and said they were looking for Shirou...
...and she was worried.
There has to be a mistake! Where's Shirou?
Nazuna?
Huh. It shouldn't matter if you're a beastman or a human as long as you stay alive, right?
That's true, but Shirou doesn't even entertain that thought.
Did you hear about the live from Alan?
Live?
Yeah!
Until the cure is done, to ease the minds of stressed beastmen...
...the cult is holding a live event.
It will be streamed all throughout Animacity!
I asked Alan if he could get you to be part of my staff.
It will pretty much be my first live, after all.
Let's think of a setlist together!
Nazuna, did you know about the Nirvasyl Syndrome?
Yeah. Alan told me to keep that info from unrelated people...
...but you're already involved.
Besides, there's nothing else I'd be hiding from you.
Really?
Probably.
If there is, I'll apologize, so spare me~
What's that about? Well, that's fine.
A live, huh... That's amazing, Nazuna! You're like a real idol now.
That's right. I'll become a real idol.
We'll make this a success and save this city!
Michiru!
I made some tea... Whoa!
Ah, no... I mean... This is...!
Ginrou-sama! Why are you here?
I have come to get closer to my followers.
I will go wherever I'm needed.
That's a quick change.
A-ah, I see...
This girl has been through a lot recently...
As expected of Ginrou-sama.
It is alright. I am sure she'll find her path.
I will be leaving now.
May you become a good beastman.
Is Ginrou-sama really all that?
Yeah...
I can't believe it's such a young girl, though.
Ah, don't worry about those things.
As long as Ginrou-sama is here...
May you become a good beastman.
You went overboard, Oogami.
Do you know what Alan is trying to do?
He's trying to turn all beastmen into humans.
I know.
Then why are you stopping me?
"I don't care about death as long as I'm a beastman"...
...not all beastmen think like that.
Even you...
But I'll make sure it doesn't come to that.
I'm dismantling Animacity.
If beastmen start rampaging because the population is increasing...
...then dispersing them is for the best.
I will meet with Prime Minister Shiramizu tomorrow.
I'm going to request for beastmen to be accepted and distributed all across Japan.
However, if a Nirvasyl Syndrome outbreak starts happening before then...
...then using the vaccine will be unavoidable.
That's...!
Alright. Do what you must in your own way.
Where could he be...?
What happened? I don't recall seeing rain today.
It's none of your business, so get lost. I'm in a bad mood.
Figured as much, since the police is looking for you.
Get on, I'll give you a ride.
I don't need it.
Don't say that.
I heard you had a fight with Sylvasta.
What did you find, Oogami?
I know this city is becoming shadier every day.
I wouldn't be fit to be The Family's boss if I didn't.
I see. It is a rather urgent matter.
I can't say humans and beastmen get along too well.
Although it's an avoidable disease...
If humans find out about it now, they'll needlessly become anxious.
I beg you to distribute beastmen as quickly and quietly as possible.
I understand how you feel.
However, I can't let any beastmen leave Animacity.
This is...
I received information about the Nirvasyl Syndrome.
I'm already taking measures.
Mayor Rose, I've been requested to protect you.
Protect me?
Well, things should be going smoothly over there...
...so just sit back and relax.
Hold on a minute! Prime Minister!
Thank you. I appreciate your cooperation, Prime Minister.
Shirou?!
Damn... That stubborn geezer...
♪～
～♪