♪～
～♪
Michiru!
Jackie! Why are you here?
This bread crust is delicious!
It doesn't just have the brown bits, it has white bits too!
Have you only eaten crusts?
It's great! This bread crust is delicious!
It's a Special Super Crust!
Y-yay, great...
Even the smell is different!
A friend of yours?
Yeah.
Ah, sorry for all the fuss.
It's really easy for you to make friends, huh.
Ginrou-sama!
Thank you for the Super Crust!
If you're hungry, you're free to come by at any time.
Ginrou-sama~!
May you become a good beastman.
May you become a good beastman!
Still... Is it okay to have so many beastmen gathered in the live event?
"Being positive and feeling festive is very important"...
...is what Alan said.
Now that you mention it, there was a festival going on when I first arrived.
It'll be broadcast live too...
...so I chose some fun songs for now.
What do you think?
Huh? Are you gonna sing this?
Is that no good?
Nazuna... You always make a dumb face when you sing this song.
What?
I mean, come on. That song isn't even in here!
Hm, that's true, but I figured it wouldn't be fitting for a live event...
That's not true!
Really?
Yeah! I wanna hear it too!
So show me
that shimmer that sparkles in the night
and fly around as much as you want
Let's run around more freely
to look up at the stars
It's decided
Damn.
I'm not just gonna choose whatever you like.
Huh? Hey.
What's this about "a revelation from the MC"?
Ah, that? That's when I'll say "Actually, I'm a human"!
Are you sure it's okay to blurt that out?
When Alan finishes the cure...
...he said it would be needed to alleviate the stress of beastmen.
I... see.
Humans and beastmen aren't all that different. They go about their lives very similarly.
We're the ones who can say that, right?
Y... Yeah...
Through the roof...?!
Don't move!
Leave this to me.
Hurry back to Animacity.
Ishizaki, thank you!
Are the boats ready?
We have 1000 freighters ready.
We should have 5000 large cruisers in the next 5 days.
That should balance out the amount of people from the cult.
Thank you.
If this city disappears, it'll be a pain for me, too.
Huh, to think you'd join forces.
The Silver Wolf Order is looking for you.
Who started the search?
I start moving before I get asked to do it, so the profits are bigger.
It seems the tanuki girl is involved, too.
It's fine if you don't wanna know, though.
Just start talking.
She was talking with that guru about the live event.
Apparently she plans to blurt out that she's a human.
Saying that "it will ease the minds of beastmen after the cure is made" or something.
What?!
Hey, Nazuna. Are you really doing that confession?
I told you.
It's needed to prevent the Nirvasyl Syndrome from taking over.
Okay...
But if Shirou hears that, I bet he'll be mad.
Why? I'm doing this for the sake of beastmen...
There's no way he'll be mad.
I wonder...
Ms. Déesse Louve.
We should be leaving soon.
Michiru can come too, right?
People will be watching.
C'mon... It's fine just for today, isn't it?
It's fine. I have something I wanna do either way.
Really?
I'll let the receptionist know you're coming...
...so don't be late, okay?
Okay!
See you later then!
This festival is more crowded than that time...
When did it...
Michiru~!
Did I scare you?
Mr. Gem?
It's Ginrou-sama's live event!
It's a festival!
Mr. Gem! Ms. Melissa!
You two made this?!
This is to show our appreciation towards Ginrou-sama.
Before this city was built, there were some things...
...that hurt deep within our hearts that we'd rather not remember.
Of course, that applies to us, too.
So we wanted to show just how much Ginrou-sama's legend...
...helped us stay afloat back then.
That's why everyone made this!
Everyone...?
Yeah! Every beastman in Animacity participated!
It carries the gratefulness of being protected for a thousand years.
It might not reach Ginrou-sama, though.
I'm sure everyone's feelings will make it through!
I'm sure Ginrou-sama would cry tears of joy.
That would be nice!
I'm sure it will!
Thank you, Michiru.
Michiru?
Where's Michiru?
Who knows? She hasn't come here yet.
Damn it. She still doesn't care about being on time.
Where is he?
Shirou...
In any case, Kuromaki will get The Family's things onto the boat.
Only the slum people are left.
It'll be easy as long as we offer money.
Mari, you're good with words.
Get as many people out of that venue as you can.
Leave it to me.
Do you need that?
Failure is not an option.
If that's the case, we'll go too.
We can't be flashy or provoke the audience.
I'll call you in case things go awry.
I'll deal with the guru myself.
Shirou!
It's almost time.
The lost beastmen patiently wait for your appearance.
You can do it, Nazuna. You'll be the real deal.
This road is swarming with police and beastmen suppresion forces.
Aside from that, the entrance to Animacity is full of inspectors.
I don't think walking there is an option, Mayor.
Are you perhaps Pinga?
As expected of the Mayor. You know your stuff.
Why are you here?
I found out things are getting pretty bad by intercepting government calls.
When I came back to investigate, I saw you being chased by humans.
It'd be a pain if you got killed before making the graves for my comrades.
And I don't want the efforts of the tanuki girl to go to waste.
Those are anti-beastmen mobile weapons.
Weapons?
Yeah. I saw those being used in anti-beastmen riots.
That's...! We must hurry to Animacity!
That's the plan!
What should I do...?
Why...
Shirou.
Don't get in my way.
The soul who walked towards
the place where light shines
together with much compassion
we'll see an endless dream
I'm sorry! The feelings you have regarding beastmen...
...I should've been able to understand.
I turned from a human to a beastman.
I knew the most about the fear of turning into someone else.
But I didn't pay attention to how you felt.
So I needed to apologize.
You...
But it's becoming confusing again.
What are you trying to do? Why do you have a gun...?
I won't get it unless you tell me!
Nazuna is my friend!
Why are you trying to...
Why...
I'm sorry.
I don't want to hurt your friend.
But this live event...
No... I've got to stop that confession from happening.
If the guru confesses she's a human...
It will trigger the Nirvasyl Syndrome.
When will she talk about her identity?
Is the confession really a trigger?
I'm sure of it. Beastmen are stubborn.
Their emotions are deeper, and their prejudices are strong.
If they find out they were tricked by those they believe in...
The shock that would cause is incomparable.
They will rampage.
So the exact opposite of what Alan told Nazuna?
Alan told her knowing this.
What? For what?
I don't know.
Either way, stopping the confession comes first.
Are you able to persuade her?
We're suddenly upside down
and the world changes around us
She flies above the audience during this song...
...then she moves to the opposite side of the stage and changes costumes. That's when...
The opposite side...
I'll fly. It'll be faster that way.
Don't provoke the audience. I'll go there later.
Got it.
I feel like crying, but I don't want to lose
So show me
that shimmer that sparkles in the night
and fly around...
Inspector...
President Alan said you would definitely come this way.
Alan?
It's a shame it's come to this.
Inspector, there's no time. Let me through.
I can't do that. You're wanted by the police.
I'll make up for that sin later!
The city is in danger!
If we don't stop this, the city will be destroyed!
What are you saying?
I want to protect all beastmen. That's really all I want!
I beg you! Don't make this city a living hell!
Phew, I made it.
There's a change in the plans. Do your confession here.
The audience is past the expected point of excitement.
Let's make every effort to move forward.
Got it.
Everyone! Are you excited?
What? This isn't in the schedule!
I'm very excited, too!
This is bad...!
Having so many people gathered here today...
Thank you so much, everyone!
May you become a good beastman!
Actually...
There's something I really want to tell everyone today.
What~?
What is it?
That's...
Nazuna!
Michiru?!
Don't do the confession!
Huh?
Please. Trust me!
Something I really want to tell everyone.
That is...
...how grateful I am for everyone that made this big Ginrou!
Thank you!
You'd better explain this later.
Yeah!
...She did it.
That's...!
Oogami!
Don't let her fool you!
She is nothing like Ginrou-sama! She is a human!
Boris?
I was being fooled, too.
She became a beastman thanks to a drug made by Sylvasta!
She pretended to be Ginrou-sama and tricked all of us!
A human dared to trick us with the sacred Ginrou!
A human?
Ginrou-sama is a human...?
No way...
Were we tricked?
She tried to trick and control all the noble beastmen!
We were tricked! By a damn human!
There is no forgiving something like this!
It's the work of a human!
Humans want to destroy beastmen using those weapons!
Nazuna!
Thank you!
Just like planned.
Damn! They keep coming...
Oogami!
This is...!
I was...
...unable to save them again...?
How am I the protector of beastmen?!
I...
...am useless...
I... I...!
Shirou?
Oogami...
Stop, Oogami!
Shirou, stop!
Shir...
Michiru!
♪～
～♪