Michiru!
Michiru... This can't be...!
Oogami...
Hey...
Hey... Michiru!
Can you do that again?
Your howling is amazing.
Mi... Michiru!
Ouch...!
Oh! Sorry!
Are your wounds okay?
Yeah... but you didn't bite my gorilla arm, so it was dangerous.
Thank you. You saved me.
Thank you, Michiru.
Oogami!
The Mayor! And Pinga!
To the city hall!
Get on!
As promised, Animacity is on lockdown.
This should ensure the safety of all citizens, right?
Don't worry, Prime Minister.
The beastmen will die as such before long.
Japan would be the first in the world to resolve the beastman problem.
So, Oogami had an outbreak like everyone else, but as soon as he bit you, he returned to normal?
That's right.
Look at this.
This is a sample from Yaba's blood that I found stored away.
I'll mix it in with Michiru's blood.
Her Beast Factor is rewriting other Beast Factors.
The rampaging Beast Factor is returning to normal. In other words, Oogami returning to normal is thanks to Michiru.
The Beast Factor in both of you has the ability to change forms at will.
If we apply that to other Beast Factors, it will result in the neutralization of the beast form rampage.
If we make a serum, we can cure the Nirvasyl Syndrome.
Really?!
The Japanese Government will not come to our aid.
This is our last chance.
To the Medical Center.
We can synthesize a serum there.
We gotta hurry.
I'm not going.
If stress is relieved, an outbreak won't happen, right?
Are you going to the city?! It's too dangerous.
I lied about me being Ginrou to everyone who believed in me.
If I don't do something, I can't forgive myself.
I'll help the girl, too.
Leave the serum to me.
Okay.
I'll protect the city.
Thank you.
When we're done...
We make a speech!
Let's go.
I'll take some blood from you. Get ready.
How long do you need?
Give me 8 hours.
If the Beast Factor Termination Vaccine spreads before then, it's over.
I'm going to stop Alan.
Don't let anyone in.
Shirou!
You have to stay.
No!
There's no use for me in waiting. Get that through your thick skull!
Where are your parents?
It'll be okay. A cure is being made now, so everyone will heal and go back to normal.
Really?
Until then, listen to music or draw a bit. Do what makes you happy so your feelings don't go out of control.
Can you do that?
Alright, let's go play with your friends.
I'll take this child with me.
Please.
Ms. Déesse Louve.
Boris...
Please forgive me. It was all under Alan's orders...
We beastmen can't defy Sylvasta's orders.
However, we are free now.
Let's run together!
There's no way I'd do that!
Stop meddling with my life...!
You are mine, Déesse Louve!
Let me go!
You're coming with me, Déesse Louve!
I'm not Déesse Louve! I am Nazuna!
You're seriously gross.
Deésse Louve...
Why...?!
Stop! I don't wanna date you!
What's all this?!
They are drones equipped with the Beast Factor Termination Vaccine.
Alan!
I'll use these on all surplus rampaging beastmen in Animacity.
You're the one who made them rampage!
What's your objective?!
Everything is part of a necessary process.
I plan to let the world know about the dreadful Nirvasyl Syndrome...
...and legitimize the usage of the Beast Factor Termination Vaccine.
This is a demonstration, so to speak.
Is that why you threw Animacity into a crisis?! Unforgivable!
Calm down! As long as we use the Termination Vaccine to eliminate the Beast Factor, everything's gonna be fine.
That's not a solution! You don't have to erase the Beast Factor. A serum is just enough!
Serum?
My blood and Nazuna's can be turned into a cure!
If we complete the serum, there'll be no need to turn beastmen into humans!
That's... I wasn't able to predict that.
I started rampaging, but I went back to normal!
So don't use the Termination Vaccine!
I see. I get what you mean now.
Leave the rest to me.
Stop it!
Ahh... There's no other way.
Shirou!
Make it stop...!
I thought you were smarter than this.
Isn't it amazing? Their precious Ginrou was actually a human...
...and after finding out, those poor beastmen went insane and started rampaging, only to be turned into humans themselves...
That's horrible...!
Are you going to bite me? So scary~
Damn it...
Don't get in my way again, please.
I won't let a filthy human like you... destroy beastmen!
Would you get those dirty paws off me?
What...?!
I'll teach you the truth about the world!
A beastman...?!
His smell is completely human...!
The Sylvasta Family has been living among humans and controlling them for generations.
Things like hiding your beastman side are easy.
Unlike you hybrid beasts, we purebreds are the real beastmen.
Take a look at a true godly wolf.
Originally, beastmen worshipped the local beasts as gods...
...and used their power for their own gain.
By refusing to mix with beasts of another nature, they kept their own blood pure.
That's what a purebred is.
Most beastmen hated being in contact with humans...
...so they let go of their original land and created a separate one with other beastmen.
Just like you and other beastmen living in this city.
Pride-born beastmen were the only ones who refused to mix with other blood and protected their pride.
This form is proof of those proud purebreds.
To think a hybrid like you calls himself a " protector"...
Your ignorance... is frightening!
You talk a lot for someone with three necks!
You're immortal too?!
Immortality is our exclusive right.
An undead ritual that can only be performed by the chosen...
...where you gather blood from a thousand wolf beastmen and pour it into your body.
Doing that grants you this power.
It seems you've happened to meet the same fate.
But you're the result of mixed blood, so after all, you're no more than a sham.
A sham...?!
Hybrids aren't even beastmen, anyways.
Things like the Nirvasyl Syndrome happen only because you're a hybrid.
The mixture of Beast Factors leads to the stress that causes rampages.
We purebreds don't have such an issue.
We will also keep ruling the world as purebreds, like always.
Controlling humans from the shadows, that is.
That's the truth about the world!
That's what you get for getting in my way.
Stop!
You're persistent!
Déesse Louve...
I'll turn a profit if I help you! So be grateful!
You're...
A mangoose...!
A mink! Mari the Mink!
May you be a good beastman!
Ginrou-sama! This way, come on!
My money!
I'm not Ginrou!
You gave us a Super Crust.
To us, anyone who feeds us when we're hungry is considered a god.
I ran in a dangerous direction!
This way!
We're surrounded!
If I knew running to save people would be like this...!
Are you alright?
Pinga!
Stop that thing! It has a drug that turns beastmen into humans!
What?!
Nazuna!
Pinga, take care of that drone!
Leave it to me!
Michiru?
Michiru!
Nazuna!
Eh? W-what's going on?
I don't know, but beastmen seem to react instinctively to this howling.
Those drones only seem to target rampaging beastmen.
If only there was a way to make this howl reach all of Animacity...
The live event!
Jackie, you and your friends should turn on as many TVs as you can in the city.
Me, Nazuna and Mari will go to the venue center and broadcast a video!
These guys are annoying.
Where were you hiding all this?!
Illegal gun trafficking must have a limit, too!
Enemy invasion! Enemy invasion!
If you get hit by the enemy, you'll turn into a human!
So the bear goes after the honey?
I hope you appreciate me being a criminal!
Go, go.
That's it!
Mari, hurry up!
Be patient! This ain't easy.
Stop your useless struggling.
Alan...!
I don't know what you're scheming, but take a good look.
Animacity is over.
Beastmen will kill each other before that serum is completed...
The city will be destroyed, and all those remaining will be turned into humans by the Termination Vaccine!
A woman bearing those arms isn't very pretty.
You're a human, so wouldn't it be better for you to just go back to normal and live your life normally?
Being a girl, a beastman, a human...
I don't give a damn about any of that!
I'll decide what's normal for me... And how I live, and if I'm pretty or not as well!
If there are beastmen who want to turn into humans, then so be it!
But the way you stripped them from the right to decide that...
It's really... Awfully...
GROSS!
That's a real shame!
Good bye, you disgusting hybrid!
Shirou!
To think you were still alive...
The people living inside me...
...they're telling me not to give up.
Those people you scoffed at for being hybrids!
Alan...
He was a beastman all along...?
Are you trying to buy some time?
That's right...!
Until I learn your tricks, that is!
There's no way...
a filthy hybrid like you...
...can match...
...my divine howl!
What?!
Incredible...!
I haven't lived a thousand years for nothing!
That's... impossible...!
This isn't a "divine howl" or anything like that!
It just serves to kill people!
Do you want to taste it again?!
Let me go...! Stop it... Please stop... Sto...!
That's...!
...the Nirvasyl Syndrome!
T... that can't be...!
You're in shambles.
What was that about "not being affected"?
I'll finish you before your reason fades away!
Someone help me! Please!
Her antibodies run through my blood.
Why... did you save me...?
I don't want to live with regrets anymore.
Michiru! All ready.
Give me that video.
No way! I have no battery?!
Seriously?! We have to charge it up!
Shirou!
Please! Can you howl?
The only one who can protect Animacity... is Ginrou!
The real one is amazing!
This is when I realized.
Me and Nazuna are different from them.
...but seeing Shirou so sad, so miserable...
...but still thinking about others...
It took some time, but the rampaging beastmen went back to normal.
Get your limited 5 photo set of the new Animacity symbol, Nazuna!
A video recorded from a hidden camera that caught Nazuna saving a kid buzzed around...
...and she became popular among beastmen and humans.
She says she didn't know there was a camera...
...but I think she definitely knew.
She's very calculating.
We protected our autonomy.
After negotiating with the Prime Minister and the Sylvasta Conglomerate...
...they reluctantly accepted.
Alan resigned as the President of Sylvasta Pharmaceutics, so it's safe to assume he's going to lay low for now.
I will change this city.
To make them understand what we are.
I will invite humans to the city as well.
And I'll have beastmen learn about humans, too.
Can you do such a thing?
It will be difficult.
But I'll take it slow.
Thankfully, I have time.
We both do.
Shirou!
Is your body okay now?
Yeah!
See?
Sorry for everything.
It's not your fault.
The cure for your beastman disease is near, too.
That's good.
You'll be able to go home.
I'm fine like this.
I'll stay here for now.
Only Nazuna and I have experience being both beastman and human.
I think there are things here that I can only accomplish the way I am right now.
Besides, I like the current me.
What will you do in this city?
I can't say for sure yet, but...
...I'll look for things only I can do.
Like playing basketball, and helping Nazuna out.
Of course, I'll help you out, too.
I don't remember asking you, though.
Say, the night I first got here, I saw Ginrou.
You were really happy about that festival, weren't you?
That's why you wanted to celebrate as Ginrou.
But wouldn't it be better to be in whatever form you want to be on from now on?
Michiru!
Let's go get some tea!
Okay!
I'll get going, then.
We might be able to change...
...this city, too.